The	O
2011	B-ORG
NCAA	I-ORG
Division	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
Men	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Ice	I-ORG
Hockey	I-ORG
Tournament	I-ORG
featured	O
the	O
Air	B-ORG
Force	I-ORG
Falcons	I-ORG
,	O
Minnesota-Duluth	B-ORG
Bulldogs	I-ORG
,	O
Union	B-ORG
Dutchmen	I-ORG
and	O
Yale	B-ORG
Bulldogs	I-ORG
.	O
	
Martin	B-PER
,	I-PER
Ralph	I-PER
G	I-PER
.	I-PER
.	O
	
Anne	B-PER
Jones	I-PER
(	I-PER
writer	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
``	O
In	B-ORG
For	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Penny	I-ORG
''	O
	
Campeonato	B-ORG
Mineiro	I-ORG
:	O
2012	B-LOC
,	O
2013	B-LOC
	
Maurice	B-PER
(	I-PER
emperor	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
''	O
Ulidia	B-LOC
megacephala	I-LOC
''	O
Loew	B-PER
,	O
1845	O
	
Theatres	B-ORG
des	I-ORG
Vampires	I-ORG
	
Some	O
visitors	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
away	O
as	O
Port	B-LOC
Arthur	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
and	O
Louisiana	B-LOC
.	O
	
Get	B-ORG
off	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Stage	I-ORG
	
Johor	B-ORG
Bahru	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
Square	I-ORG
	
James	B-PER
MacLellan	I-PER
Brown	I-PER
	
House	B-PER
of	I-PER
Glücksburg	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Lindley	B-PER
Beckworth	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
Unopposed	O
''	O
'	O
	
Arnold	B-PER
Allan	I-PER
Cecil	I-PER
Keppel	I-PER
,	I-PER
8th	I-PER
Earl	I-PER
of	I-PER
Albemarle	I-PER
(	O
1858–1942	O
)	O
	
Happy]]	O
''	O
–	O
Pharrell	B-PER
Williams	I-PER
	
His	O
son	O
Murad	B-PER
II	I-PER
Bey	I-PER
made	O
this	O
his	O
primary	O
residence	O
,	O
dwelling	O
there	O
almost	O
permanently	O
.	O
	
*Director	O
,	O
the	O
Black	B-ORG
Dog	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
With	O
the	O
Art	B-PER
Farmer	I-PER
/	O
Benny	B-PER
Golson	I-PER
Jazztet	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Matfield	B-LOC
Green	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kansas	I-LOC
	
Frans	B-PER
Banninck	I-PER
Cocq	I-PER
	
Alla	B-PER
Beknazarova	I-PER
/	O
Vladimir	B-PER
Zuev	I-PER
	
He	O
was	O
in	O
private	O
practice	O
in	O
Berks	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC
from	O
1949	O
to	O
1970	O
.	O
	
São	B-LOC
Bartolomeu	I-LOC
River	I-LOC
	
Aboudeïa	B-ORG
–	O
Salamat	B-LOC
Region	I-LOC
	
J.	B-PER
Bob	I-PER
Kelly	I-PER
	
Keeble	B-ORG
v	I-ORG
Hickeringill	I-ORG
''	O
	
18	O
July	O
–	O
Paul	B-PER
Foot	I-PER
,	O
journalist	O
and	O
nephew	O
of	O
former	O
Labour	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
leader	O
Michael	B-PER
Foot	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1937	O
)	O
	
Govind	B-ORG
Chandra	I-ORG
Pandey	I-ORG
(	O
1923	O
)	O
	
''	O
Sphingonaepiopsis	B-LOC
kuldjaensis	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Graeser	O
,	O
1892	O
)	O
	
San	B-PER
Miguel	I-PER
Beermen	I-PER
	
Coming	O
on	O
twice	O
as	O
a	O
substitute	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
selected	O
to	O
start	O
in	O
the	O
semi-final	O
loss	O
to	O
Brazil	B-ORG
.	O
	
Adnan	B-PER
Sami	I-PER
,	O
Asha	B-PER
Bhosle	I-PER
	
Lee	B-PER
Eun-ju	I-PER
...	O
Kyeong-woo	O
	
''	O
Tenkai	B-ORG
Knights	I-ORG
''	O
	
Estadio	B-ORG
Regional	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
Antofagasta	I-ORG
,	O
Antofagasta	B-LOC
	
;	O
Teams	O
losing	O
Copa	B-ORG
del	I-ORG
Rey	I-ORG
first	O
round	O
	
**	O
Battle	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Drocourt-Queant	I-ORG
Line	I-ORG
2–3	O
September	O
1918	O
	
The	O
Late	B-ORG
Baroque	I-ORG
building	O
was	O
left	O
incomplete	O
when	O
the	O
Empress	B-PER
Elizabeth	I-PER
came	O
to	O
the	O
throne	O
in	O
1742	O
.	O
	
Proc.	B-ORG
Inst.	I-ORG
Mech	I-ORG
Eng	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
Vol	O
180,1966	O
.	O
	
**	O
Kyoto	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Museum	I-ORG
(	O
early	O
production	O
cast	O
)	O
	
Decker	B-LOC
Prairie	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
	
Digimon	B-PER
Data	I-PER
Squad	I-PER
''	O
-	O
DemiDevimon	B-ORG
,	O
Mojyamon	B-ORG
,	O
Tsunomon	B-ORG
	
Boys	B-ORG
from	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Blackstuff	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1980–1982	O
)	O
	
*From	O
the	O
album	O
I	B-ORG
Think	I-ORG
We	I-ORG
're	I-ORG
All	I-ORG
Bozos	I-ORG
on	I-ORG
This	I-ORG
Bus	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
August	O
1971	O
	
Zulu	B-LOC
golden	I-LOC
mole	I-LOC
	
/	O
Lauren	B-PER
Montgomery	I-PER
/	O
Brandon	B-PER
Vietti	I-PER
	
Micah	B-LOC
P.	I-LOC
Hinson	I-LOC
and	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Opera	I-LOC
Circuit	I-LOC
''	O
	
Alicia	B-PER
Koplowitz	I-PER
,	I-PER
7th	I-PER
Marquise	I-PER
of	I-PER
Bellavista	I-PER
	
Lambda	B-ORG
Kappa	I-ORG
Sigma	I-ORG
,	O
founded	O
in	O
1913	O
at	O
Massachusetts	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Pharmacy	I-ORG
.	O
	
Route	B-ORG
311	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Virginia–West	I-ORG
Virginia	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''As	O
of	O
UAE	B-ORG
Pro	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
:	O
''	O
	
Among	O
many	O
artists	O
who	O
recorded	O
this	O
song	O
were	O
Al	B-PER
Jolson	I-PER
and	O
Billy	B-PER
Murray	I-PER
.	O
	
Córdoba	B-LOC
Province	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Argentina	I-LOC
	
In	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
Marc	B-PER
Surer	I-PER
prevailed	O
for	O
the	O
works	O
.	O
	
Fan	B-PER
,	I-PER
Ye	I-PER
.	O
	
Robinson	B-PER
,	I-PER
Agnes	I-PER
Mary	I-PER
Frances	I-PER
(	O
1897	O
)	O
.	O
	
Buy	B-ORG
U	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Drank	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Shawty	I-ORG
Snappin	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
(	O
2007	O
/	O
ft	O
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Aprilia	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Western	B-LOC
Region	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
British	I-LOC
Railways	I-LOC
	
Going	B-ORG
Home	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Jaipur	B-LOC
(	O
Palace	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Winds	I-ORG
)	O
	
It	O
lies	O
north-west	O
of	O
Kowalewo	B-LOC
Pomorskie	I-LOC
,	O
north-west	O
of	O
Golub-Dobrzyń	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
north-east	O
of	O
Toruń	B-LOC
.	O
	
Emoryville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Novak	B-PER
Djokovic	I-PER
''	O
'6–1	O
,	O
7–5	O
	
Interview	O
with	O
Granta	B-ORG
(	O
October	O
5	O
,	O
2013	O
)	O
	
Will	B-PER
Ferrell	I-PER
,	O
Caroline	B-PER
Rhea	I-PER
	
:	O
*331	O
Trevor	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
(	O
2000–06	O
)	O
	
São	B-LOC
Simão	I-LOC
-	O
1.343	O
billion	O
	
Hans	B-PER
Jørgen	I-PER
Hammer	I-PER
	
Pike	B-ORG
Bay	I-ORG
Township	I-ORG
,	O
Cass	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Elissa	B-PER
(	I-PER
Lebanese	I-PER
singer	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Stony	B-LOC
Plain	I-LOC
'	O
''	O
(	O
587	O
)	O
'	O
''	O
-250	O
268	O
980	O
	
The	O
supporting	O
cast	O
features	O
Robert	B-PER
Young	I-PER
,	O
Robert	B-PER
Stack	I-PER
,	O
Frank	B-PER
Morgan	I-PER
,	O
Dan	B-PER
Dailey	I-PER
,	O
Ward	B-PER
Bond	I-PER
and	O
Maria	B-PER
Ouspenskaya	I-PER
.	O
	
Finsch	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
rufous	I-LOC
thrush	I-LOC
	
''	O
Play	B-ORG
Something	I-ORG
Country	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
3:10	O
	
Ioan	B-PER
P.	I-PER
Culianu	I-PER
	
The	O
song	O
was	O
a	O
hit	O
when	O
first	O
published	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
covered	O
by	O
numerous	O
artists	O
including	O
Ben	B-PER
Bernie	I-PER
and	I-PER
His	I-PER
Hotel	I-PER
Roosevelt	I-PER
Orchestra	I-PER
,	O
Annette	B-PER
Hanshaw	I-PER
,	O
Ben	B-PER
Selvin	I-PER
&	I-PER
His	I-PER
Orchestra	I-PER
and	O
Belle	B-PER
Baker	I-PER
.	O
	
Andrew	B-PER
Ilie	I-PER
''	O
(	O
Second	O
Round	O
)	O
	
The	O
song	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
oft-covered	O
song	O
on	O
American	B-ORG
Idol	I-ORG
''	O
with	O
singers	O
Tamyra	B-PER
Gray	I-PER
and	O
Fantasia	B-PER
Barrino	I-PER
covering	O
it	O
.	O
	
Australian	B-LOC
sawtail	I-LOC
catshark	I-LOC
	
Latvian	B-ORG
Higher	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
:	O
2012	B-LOC
	
They	O
were	O
Soviet	B-LOC
s	O
purchased	O
in	O
the	O
1950s	O
.	O
	
Luther	B-ORG
Burbank	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Arts	I-ORG
	
The	O
Free	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Division	I-ORG
at	O
Bloemfontein	B-LOC
	
Barbara	B-PER
Schett	I-PER
Amanda	B-PER
Coetzer	I-PER
Jana	B-PER
Novotná	I-PER
Lindsay	B-PER
Davenport	I-PER
	
''	O
Trịnh	B-PER
Tùng	I-PER
''	O
'	O
-	O
Ruled	O
1570–1623	O
.	O
	
Grantsville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
	
A	O
retail	O
store	O
where	O
guests	O
can	O
shop	O
for	O
Sesame	B-ORG
Street	I-ORG
themed	O
souvenirs	O
and	O
apparel	O
.	O
	
Skyscraper	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
	
Verne	B-PER
Troyer	I-PER
(	O
episode	O
3	O
)	O
	
He	O
was	O
appointed	O
High	B-PER
Sheriff	I-PER
of	I-PER
Worcestershire	I-PER
for	O
1584	O
.	O
	
Knox	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
	
Sharpsburg	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
North	I-LOC
Carolina	I-LOC
	
Songdin	B-LOC
(	O
622	O
)	O
	
María	B-PER
Cayetana	I-PER
de	I-PER
Silva	I-PER
,	I-PER
13th	I-PER
Duchess	I-PER
of	I-PER
Alba	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Pushing	B-PER
Daisies	I-PER
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
and	O
Ph.D.	O
degrees	O
from	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Texas	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
Austin	I-ORG
.	O
	
Before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Germany	B-LOC
.	O
	
Tribhuvan	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
Nepal	B-LOC
	
Rudniki	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Białystok	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Politics	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Edinburgh	I-ORG
	
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Lethbridge	I-ORG
Community	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
	
Rufus	B-ORG
Does	I-ORG
Judy	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
Carnegie	I-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
''	O
	
Louis	B-PER
I	I-PER
,	I-PER
Count	I-PER
of	I-PER
Étampes	I-PER
	
Auto	B-ORG
Clearing	I-ORG
Motor	I-ORG
Speedway	I-ORG
,	O
Saskatoon	B-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Bangalore	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
McKinney	B-ORG
Avenue	I-ORG
Transit	I-ORG
Authority	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Kevin	B-ORG
Harvick	I-ORG
Incorporated	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Aaron	B-ORG
``	I-ORG
Wheelz	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
Fotheringham	I-ORG
,	O
Nikki	B-PER
Yanofsky	I-PER
and	O
others	O
performed	O
.	O
	
Mrs	O
Herbert	B-PER
Strang	I-PER
(	O
and	O
Apuleius	B-PER
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Caio	B-PER
Zampieri	I-PER
''	O
'	O
7–6	O
(	O
7–3	O
)	O
,	O
5–7	O
,	O
7–6	O
(	O
7–4	O
)	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
Guinea	I-LOC
.	O
	
Susan	B-PER
Rasinski	I-PER
McCaw	I-PER
–	O
Political	O
appointee	O
	
Wexford	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Michigan	I-LOC
	
Serge	B-PER
and	I-PER
Beate	I-PER
Klarsfeld	I-PER
	
Ystads	B-ORG
IF	I-ORG
22	O
8	O
8	O
6	O
37-33	O
32	O
	
Maribel	B-ORG
Rodríguez	I-ORG
Hernández	I-ORG
(	O
2001–2002	O
)	O
''Arecibo	O
''	O
	
'	O
''	O
Morbidelli	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
FC	B-ORG
Lokomotiv	I-ORG
Chita	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Sri	B-PER
Vidyaranya	I-PER
:	O
Panchadashi	O
.	O
	
Stockton	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
	
Mayor	B-PER
of	I-PER
Wellington	I-PER
–	O
Frank	B-PER
Kitts	I-PER
	
Trajan	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Forum	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
James	B-PER
Dreyfus	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Red	B-LOC
phalarope	I-LOC
,	O
''Phalaropus	O
fulicarius	O
''	O
	
Spring	B-LOC
Grove	I-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Houston	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Minnesota	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Nicol	B-PER
David	I-PER
''	O
'11-5	O
,	O
11-4	O
,	O
11-9	O
	
Central	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG
Museum	I-ORG
	
He	O
died	O
in	O
Munich	B-LOC
.	O
	
Indonesian	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
	
He	O
is	O
a	O
Democrat	B-ORG
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Ernests	B-PER
Gulbis	I-PER
[24]	O
''	O
'	O
	
37	O
/	O
1	O
,	O
Make	B-ORG
Me	I-ORG
an	I-ORG
Instrument	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Your	I-ORG
Peace	I-ORG
.	O
	
Comanche	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Oklahoma	I-LOC
	
''	O
Missing	B-ORG
You	I-ORG
''	O
	
He	O
served	O
as	O
Chief	B-PER
Justice	I-PER
of	I-PER
India	I-PER
from	O
1943	O
to	O
1947	O
.	O
	
The	O
historian	O
James	B-PER
Wycliffe	I-PER
Headlam	I-PER
was	O
his	O
younger	O
brother	O
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Staple	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
8:66	O
.	O
	
They	O
have	O
three	O
daughters	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
writer	O
Rhiannon	B-PER
Lassiter	I-PER
.	O
	
P.S.1	B-ORG
Contemporary	I-ORG
Art	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
	
Thuridilla	B-LOC
gracilis	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Risbec	O
,	O
1928	O
)	O
	
I	B-ORG
Am	I-ORG
Not	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Human	I-ORG
Being	I-ORG
II	I-ORG
''	O
	
``	O
And	B-ORG
You	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Yes	B-ORG
,	O
from	O
Close	B-ORG
to	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Edge	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
1972	O
)	O
	
''	O
Prime	B-ORG
Time	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1977	O
)	O
	
Westward	B-ORG
Islet	I-ORG
,	O
in	O
the	O
Pitcairn	B-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
	
``	O
Danza	B-ORG
Kuduro	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Don	B-PER
Omar	I-PER
feat	O
.	O
	
Steve	B-PER
Robson	I-PER
—	O
songwriting	O
,	O
production	O
	
**	O
Vietnam	B-ORG
during	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Second	I-ORG
World	I-ORG
War	I-ORG
	
Paraclete	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Grenada	I-LOC
	
Stephen	B-PER
(	O
1162–1163	O
)	O
	
All	O
songs	O
by	O
Ray	B-PER
Davies	I-PER
,	O
except	O
as	O
noted	O
	
She	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
NY	I-LOC
.	O
	
Hamilton	B-ORG
Public	I-ORG
Library	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Ontario	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Juan	B-PER
de	I-PER
Araujo	I-PER
(	O
1646–1712	O
)	O
	
He	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Canada	B-ORG
men	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
national	I-ORG
volleyball	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
.	O
	
''	O
Crossroads	B-ORG
''	O
(	O
1964–1988	O
,	O
2001–2003	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Stuart	B-PER
MacGill	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
Pat	B-PER
Hennen	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
``	O
A	B-ORG
Pretty	I-ORG
Girl	I-ORG
Is	I-ORG
Like	I-ORG
A	B-ORG
Melody	I-ORG
''	O
w.m	O
.	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
China	B-LOC
.	O
	
Marguerite	B-PER
Duras	I-PER
,	O
author	O
	
Falkenberg	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Märkisch-Oderland	I-LOC
	
1999	O
:	O
''Le	O
Costume	O
''	O
by	O
Can	B-PER
Themba	I-PER
	
Claude	B-ORG
Antoine	I-ORG
Valdec	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
Lessart	I-ORG
	
:	O
:	O
:	O
:	O
''	O
B.	B-LOC
''	O
	
Banco	B-ORG
à	I-ORG
Bangkok	I-ORG
pour	I-ORG
OSS	I-ORG
117	I-ORG
''	O
	
Sărulești	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Călărași	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Olli	B-PER
Tuominen	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
''	O
Zelleria	B-LOC
mystarcha	I-LOC
''	O
Meyrick	O
,	O
1893	O
	
''	O
Campeonato	B-ORG
Maranhense	I-ORG
:	O
32	O
''	O
'	O
	
BP	B-ORG
Ford	I-ORG
Abu	I-ORG
Dhabi	I-ORG
World	I-ORG
Rally	I-ORG
Team	I-ORG
	
1929-30	B-ORG
Kangaroo	I-ORG
tour	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Great	I-ORG
Britain	I-ORG
	
San	B-LOC
Lorenzo	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
	
Andreessen	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Glenn	B-PER
Frey	I-PER
-	O
``	O
Glenn	B-ORG
Frey	I-ORG
Live	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1993	O
)	O
	
Starring	O
Nick	B-PER
Hancock	I-PER
,	O
Andrew	B-PER
Sachs	I-PER
	
Oak	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Illinois	I-LOC
	
Massachusetts	B-ORG
Route	I-ORG
3A	I-ORG
	
Aborigines	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Protection	I-ORG
Society	I-ORG
	
Albanchez	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Mágina	I-LOC
	
The	B-ORG
Beatles	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Hollywood	I-ORG
Bowl	I-ORG
''	O
[12]	O
	
London	B-ORG
Symphony	I-ORG
Orchestra	I-ORG
cond	O
.	O
	
2009	B-ORG
Allstate	I-ORG
Sugar	I-ORG
Bowl	I-ORG
	
1	O
–	O
1	O
(	O
Egypt	B-LOC
;	O
30	O
May	O
1990	O
)	O
	
Hartford	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Connecticut	I-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
	
George	B-PER
Caleb	I-PER
Bingham	I-PER
(	O
1811–1879	O
)	O
,	O
painter	O
	
''	O
The	B-ORG
Inefficiency	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Humans	I-ORG
''	O
7	O
''	O
(	O
1998	O
Thick	B-ORG
)	O
	
However	O
his	O
stay	O
at	O
Saltergate	B-ORG
lasted	O
only	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
making	O
16	O
appearances	O
in	O
total	O
before	O
joining	O
Derby	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
in	O
January	O
1956	O
for	O
a	O
fee	O
of	O
£1,500	O
.	O
	
Rock	B-LOC
Springs	I-LOC
(	O
99.6	O
%	O
)	O
	
Swaraj	B-PER
Prakash	I-PER
Gupta	I-PER
	
Girl	B-ORG
Guides	I-ORG
South	I-ORG
Africa	I-ORG
	
Worth	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Sussex	I-LOC
	
*01600	O
—	O
Monmouth	B-LOC
(	O
MO0	O
)	O
	
The	O
damage	O
necessitated	O
a	O
return	O
to	O
Pearl	B-LOC
Harbor	I-LOC
for	O
repairs	O
.	O
	
Tyler	B-ORG
courthouse	I-ORG
shooting	I-ORG
	
He	O
fought	O
in	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
World	I-ORG
War	I-ORG
between	O
1914	O
and	O
1918	O
.	O
	
Inti	B-LOC
Watana	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Urubamba	I-LOC
	
Eslamabad	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Firuzabad	I-LOC
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Cerro	B-LOC
Gordo	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Illinois	I-LOC
and	O
attended	O
Stanford	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
from	O
1913-1919	O
.	O
	
He	O
was	O
a	O
long-serving	O
sports	B-ORG
anchor	B-ORG
and	O
Executive	B-ORG
Producer	I-ORG
for	O
WJAC-TV	B-ORG
in	O
Pennsylvania	B-LOC
.	O
	
Michael	B-PER
Jordan	I-PER
,	O
Scottie	B-PER
Pippen	I-PER
(	O
37	O
)	O
	
Nadăș	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Aita	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
They	O
are	O
named	O
for	O
Robert	B-PER
Carmichael	I-PER
.	O
	
2013	B-ORG
Lahad	I-ORG
Datu	I-ORG
standoff	I-ORG
	
Test	B-PER
the	I-PER
Nation	I-PER
	
The	B-ORG
Dixie	I-ORG
Dead	I-ORG
(	O
2013	O
)	O
	
George	B-PER
Hunter	I-PER
-	O
1964	O
	
Harpers	B-LOC
Ferry	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
	
Events	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
'	O
''	O
1805	O
in	O
Austria	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
''	O
Live	B-ORG
Is	I-ORG
Beautiful	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2008	O
)	O
	
16th	B-ORG
Troop	I-ORG
Carrier	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
:	O
attached	O
14	O
November	O
1954	O
–	O
8	O
July	O
1955	O
	
''	O
Bobby	B-ORG
Jones	I-ORG
Gospel	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2016-present	O
)	O
	
Pau	B-LOC
,	O
France	B-LOC
,	O
1960	O
	
''	O
I	B-ORG
Think	I-ORG
I	B-ORG
'm	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Love	I-ORG
with	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
''	O
	
In	O
January	O
2000	O
,	O
she	O
married	O
Roman	B-PER
Skorniakov	I-PER
.	O
	
Stephen	B-PER
Finlay	I-PER
...	O
Policeman	O
	
''	O
Maple	B-ORG
Leaf	I-ORG
Wrestling	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
Tennis	B-ORG
Borussia	I-ORG
Berlin	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Henry	B-PER
Clifford	I-PER
,	I-PER
1st	I-PER
Earl	I-PER
of	I-PER
Cumberland	I-PER
,	I-PER
11th	I-PER
Baron	I-PER
de	I-PER
Clifford	I-PER
(	O
1493–1542	O
)	O
	
Albert	B-PER
Berdini	I-PER
of	I-PER
Sarteano	I-PER
	
The	O
case	O
involved	O
negotiations	O
over	O
a	O
property	O
in	O
Jamaica	B-LOC
.	O
	
Meigs	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Muskingum	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ohio	I-LOC
	
''	O
The	O
900	O
Number	O
''	O
by	O
DJ	B-PER
Mark	I-PER
the	I-PER
45	I-PER
King	I-PER
featuring	O
Lakim	B-PER
Shabazz	I-PER
	
***	O
Dravida	B-ORG
Munnetra	I-ORG
Kazhagam	I-ORG
25px	O
	
''	O
Charaxes	B-LOC
protoclea	I-LOC
azota	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Hewitson	O
,	O
1877	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Maverick	B-PER
Viñales	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
Honda	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Ili	B-LOC
Kazakh	I-LOC
Autonomous	I-LOC
Prefecture	I-LOC
	
Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Cubao	I-LOC
	
Michael	B-PER
van	I-PER
Gerwen	I-PER
(	O
93.47	O
)	O
	
Saline	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Illinois	I-LOC
	
''	O
Sultanate	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Rûm	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Kilij	B-PER
Arslan	I-PER
I	I-PER
(	O
1092–1107	O
)	O
	
Johor	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Legislative	I-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
!	O
!	O
	
``	O
Only	B-ORG
Wan	I-ORG
na	I-ORG
Be	I-ORG
with	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
''	O
	
Balboa	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
San	I-LOC
Francisco	I-LOC
	
**	O
''	O
Zea	B-LOC
luxurians	I-LOC
''	O
	
Partnoy	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Frank	I-ORG
.	O
	
John	B-PER
Arnot	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
Jesus	B-ORG
Killing	I-ORG
Machine	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1994	O
)	O
	
Frederik	B-PER
Christian	I-PER
Stoud	I-PER
Platou	I-PER
	
He	O
died	O
in	O
Munich	B-LOC
on	O
26	O
March	O
1754	O
.	O
	
Doubleday	B-ORG
(	O
Garden	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC
)	O
.	O
	
Dragan	B-PER
Džajić	I-PER
(	O
2004	O
)	O
	
On	O
5	O
February	O
2009	O
,	O
he	O
earned	O
his	O
first	O
call-up	O
to	O
the	O
France	B-ORG
under-21	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
.	O
	
Ose	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Skye	I-LOC
	
She	O
is	O
a	O
resident	O
of	O
Somerset	B-LOC
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Gönyeli	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
Cyrus	B-PER
William	I-PER
Beales	I-PER
	
|	O
Aja	B-PER
West	I-PER
&	I-PER
Friends	I-PER
	
Katalin	B-PER
Szili	I-PER
(	O
1956–	O
)	O
	
''	O
Prolita	B-LOC
sexpunctella	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Fabricius	O
,	O
1794	O
)	O
	
She	O
was	O
completed	O
on	O
18	O
January	O
1820	O
at	O
Plymouth	B-ORG
Dockyard	I-ORG
.	O
	
Algona	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Washington	I-LOC
	
Mohammed	B-PER
Aziz	I-PER
,	O
Sadhana	B-PER
Sargam	I-PER
	
Fareham	B-LOC
(	O
See	O
also	O
1489	O
)	O
	
Cedar-Riverside	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Minneapolis	I-LOC
	
''	O
September	O
12	O
''	O
–	O
Eek	B-PER
!	I-PER
The	I-PER
Cat	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
David	B-PER
Ferrer	I-PER
[7]	O
''	O
'	O
	
Lakefield	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Luce	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Its	O
first	O
appearance	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
1996	B-ORG
Apertura	I-ORG
.	O
	
Ken	B-PER
Piesse	I-PER
(	O
2004	O
)	O
.	O
	
November	O
2013–January	O
2014	O
:	O
''Stasis	O
,	O
''	O
Trine	B-PER
Søndergaard	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Murielle	B-PER
Ahouré	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Hydronebrius	B-LOC
''	O
Jakovlev	O
,	O
1897	O
	
Widacz	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Strzyżów	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Nenad	B-PER
Stavrić	I-PER
(	O
2001–06	O
)	O
	
Willie	B-PER
Hernández	I-PER
,	O
2012	O
	
Caroline	B-PER
Elam	I-PER
:	O
March	O
1987	O
–	O
July	O
2002	O
	
Călineasa	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Someșul	I-LOC
Cald	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
Events	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
'	O
''	O
2010	O
in	O
Japan	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
.	O
	
August	B-PER
Hermann	I-PER
Francke	I-PER
(	O
1953	O
,	O
2013	O
)	O
	
Ann	B-PER
Way	I-PER
...	O
Mrs.	O
Clall	O
	
St.	B-LOC
Mary	I-LOC
's	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Maryland	I-LOC
	
Naas	B-PER
Botha	I-PER
as	O
himself	O
	
The	O
main	O
opposition	O
parties	O
of	O
Fine	B-ORG
Gael	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
Labour	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
were	O
also	O
in	O
favour	O
.	O
	
Sajid	B-LOC
dynasty	I-LOC
(	O
889	O
/	O
890–929	O
)	O
of	O
Sogdian	B-LOC
origin	O
	
''	O
Oor	B-PER
Wullie	I-PER
''	O
(	O
1936–	O
)	O
by	O
Dudley	B-PER
D.	I-PER
Watkins	I-PER
and	O
others	O
(	O
Scotland	B-LOC
)	O
	
Five	O
years	O
later	O
,	O
in	O
1939	O
,	O
Edern	B-LOC
was	O
abolished	O
and	O
incorporated	O
into	O
Nefyn	B-LOC
.	O
	
Othman	B-PER
Hadi	I-PER
Al	I-PER
Maqboul	I-PER
al-Amri	I-PER
	
Electoral	B-LOC
district	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Macquarie	I-LOC
	
''	O
Chilo	B-LOC
phragmitella	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Hübner	O
,	O
1805	O
)	O
	
Santo	B-LOC
Antônio	I-LOC
do	I-LOC
Caiuá	I-LOC
	
``	O
In	B-ORG
Pieces	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Shannon	B-PER
Noll	I-PER
	
Wey	B-LOC
and	I-LOC
Godalming	I-LOC
Navigations	I-LOC
	
Martin	B-LOC
Ledge	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Massachusetts	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
Henry	B-PER
Rollins	I-PER
–	O
Robotman	B-PER
	
Danny	B-PER
Brown	I-PER
-	O
Performer	O
	
Alfian	B-PER
Eko	I-PER
Prasetya	I-PER
Shella	B-PER
Devi	I-PER
Aulia	I-PER
	
Johnny	B-PER
McCarthy	I-PER
(	I-PER
baseball	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Kenneth	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Lawrence	I-PER
	
Girls	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
(	O
1886	O
)	O
,	O
Brooklyn	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Cameron	B-PER
Crowe	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
(	O
Languages	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Malawi	I-ORG
)	O
	
Virwe	B-LOC
(	O
567	O
inhabitants	O
)	O
	
Scouting	B-ORG
Ireland	I-ORG
S.A.I	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
Iberian	B-LOC
ribbed	I-LOC
newt	I-LOC
(	O
''Pleurodeles	O
waltl	O
''	O
)	O
	
''	O
'With	O
Robert	B-PER
Fuller	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Governor	B-PER
of	I-PER
Maine	I-PER
:	O
	
Discovered	O
in	O
1852	O
at	O
Cermiky	O
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
Tschermig	O
in	O
Bohemia	B-LOC
.	O
	
Lake	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Banyoles	I-LOC
and	O
S'Agaró	B-ORG
	
Douglas	B-PER
Allen	I-PER
Booth	I-PER
	
Federal	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Somalia	I-ORG
(	O
since	O
August	O
2012	O
)	O
	
Antwaan	B-PER
Randle	I-PER
El	I-PER
	
''	O
Arthur	B-ORG
''	O
(	O
1996–present	O
)	O
	
Bartholomew	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
(	O
north-northeast	O
)	O
	
Giovanni	B-PER
Battista	I-PER
Buonamente	I-PER
	
1-0	O
Stefano	B-PER
Borgonovo	I-PER
(	O
18	O
)	O
	
*Format	O
:	O
VHS	B-PER
,	O
DVD	B-ORG
(	O
2003	O
)	O
	
Evans	B-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
is	O
nearby	O
.	O
	
''	O
Strugglin	O
'	O
Years	O
''	O
(	O
Tim	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
)	O
-	O
2:46	O
	
Binary	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
John	B-PER
Laurie	I-PER
as	O
Private	B-PER
Frazer	I-PER
	
These	O
remarks	O
earned	O
him	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
criticism	O
because	O
seemingly	O
he	O
had	O
swerved	O
from	O
his	O
famous	O
Logic	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Scientific	I-ORG
Discovery	I-ORG
.	O
	
A	O
year	O
later	O
,	O
in	O
1955	O
,	O
they	O
designed	O
the	O
Hawthorne	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
in	O
Hawthorne	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
.	O
	
File:51	O
INF	O
DIV	O
51st	B-ORG
Infantry	I-ORG
Division	I-ORG
	
William	B-ORG
Houstoun	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Peter	B-PER
Thiel	I-PER
serves	O
as	O
its	O
chairman	O
.	O
	
*143	O
,	O
111	O
,	O
110	O
Dave	B-PER
Harold	I-PER
	
•	O
Zaječiće	B-LOC
(	O
185	O
)	O
	
Navia	B-LOC
caurensis	I-LOC
''	O
L.B	O
.	O
	
Both	O
maps	O
were	O
engraved	O
by	O
Willem	B-PER
Hondius	I-PER
.	O
	
October	O
7	O
,	O
1989	O
at	O
SkyDome	B-ORG
	
Emperor	B-PER
Taizong	I-PER
of	I-PER
Liao	I-PER
	
1994	B-ORG
Major	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
Baseball	I-ORG
season	I-ORG
	
(	O
1974	O
,	O
Margaret	B-ORG
)	O
	
Michelle	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Howard	I-PER
(	O
1998	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
North	B-LOC
Dakota	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
Heliura	B-LOC
rhodocryptoides	I-LOC
''	O
Draudt	O
,	O
1931	O
	
''	O
2–	O
''	O
Newberry	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Nevada	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
:241	O
-	O
(	O
0-7	O
)	O
XXXXXX	O
Larissa	B-LOC
(	O
and	O
area	O
)	O
	
(	O
featuring	O
Yuridia	B-PER
)	O
-	O
3:52	O
	
Stoke-on-Trent	B-LOC
,	O
Newcastle-under-Lyme	B-LOC
,	O
Kidsgrove	B-LOC
	
Extravadanses	O
in	O
Castres	B-LOC
in	O
July	O
.	O
	
Fidesz	B-ORG
–	I-ORG
Hungarian	I-ORG
Civic	I-ORG
Union	I-ORG
	
Cenwalh	B-PER
of	I-PER
Wessex	I-PER
	
*7	O
November	O
1666	O
:	O
John	B-PER
Arnold	I-PER
,	O
of	O
Llanvihangel	B-LOC
Court	I-LOC
	
``	O
The	O
Visit	O
''	O
(	O
Pat	B-PER
Martino	I-PER
)	O
–	O
4:25	O
	
Songs	B-ORG
from	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Movies	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
More	I-ORG
''	O
	
Paul	B-PER
Maholm	I-PER
(	O
9–7	O
)	O
	
Paradise	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Victoria	B-PER
Pendleton	I-PER
''	O
'	O
''	O
Jessica	B-PER
Varnish	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Irchester	B-LOC
-	O
Irthlingborough	B-LOC
-	O
Isham	B-LOC
Islip	B-LOC
	
The	B-ORG
Eternal	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
band	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
St	B-ORG
Ann	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
	
**	O
Trail	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Tears	I-LOC
,	O
1830–1838	O
	
''	O
Teniorhinus	B-LOC
niger	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Druce	O
,	O
1910	O
)	O
	
Galway	B-LOC
,	O
Republic	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Ireland	I-LOC
	
Creole	B-ORG
cottage	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
architectural	O
style	O
	
**	O
'	O
''	O
Westerlo	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
7-1	O
Zulte	B-ORG
Waregem	I-ORG
(	O
4-0	O
at	O
half-time	O
)	O
(	O
7	O
May	O
2011	O
)	O
.	O
	
Arun	B-PER
Govil	I-PER
,	O
Tanuja	B-PER
,	O
Amjad	B-PER
Khan	I-PER
	
Johann	B-PER
Heinrich	I-PER
von	I-PER
Thünen	I-PER
	
It	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
318	O
during	O
the	O
second	O
General	B-ORG
Elections	I-ORG
.	O
	
Resident	O
in	O
Islamabad	B-LOC
unless	O
otherwise	O
noted	O
	
Science	B-ORG
Fiction	I-ORG
Museum	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Hall	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Fame	I-ORG
,	O
Seattle	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Washington	I-ORG
,	O
founded	O
in	O
2004	O
.	O
	
High	B-LOC
Desert	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
Olga	B-PER
Boznańska	I-PER
,	O
painter	O
	
Little	B-LOC
red	I-LOC
flying	I-LOC
fox	I-LOC
	
Cabinet	B-ORG
Office	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Sri	I-ORG
Lanka	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Their	O
first	O
retail	O
store	O
was	O
set	O
up	O
at	O
Shaw	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Centre	I-ORG
on	O
Scotts	B-LOC
Road	I-LOC
.	O
	
Grantham	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
–	O
online	O
	
'	O
''	O
With	O
Billy	B-PER
Strayhorn	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
U.S.	B-ORG
Route	I-ORG
278	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Alabama	I-ORG
	
IT	B-PER
Botham	I-PER
5	O
/	O
41	O
	
Prime	B-ORG
Minister	I-ORG
:	O
Dato	B-PER
'	I-PER
Seri	I-PER
Najib	I-PER
Tun	I-PER
Abdul	I-PER
Razak	I-PER
	
6	O
May	O
2012	O
at	O
NSC	B-ORG
``	I-ORG
Olimpiyskiy	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
,	O
Kiev	B-LOC
	
James	B-PER
B.	I-PER
Edwards	I-PER
	
His	O
death	O
was	O
profiled	O
in	O
an	O
episode	O
of	O
Unsolved	B-ORG
Mysteries	I-ORG
''	O
.	O
	
Herschel	B-ORG
Museum	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Astronomy	I-ORG
,	O
Bath	B-LOC
	
''	O
Coleophora	B-LOC
therinella	I-LOC
''	O
Tengstrom	O
,	O
1848	O
	
António	B-PER
Dias	I-PER
de	I-PER
Oliveira	I-PER
	
Alain	B-PER
Anen	I-PER
,	O
Aly	B-PER
Doerfel	I-PER
,	O
Romain	B-PER
Manelli	I-PER
,	O
Remo	B-PER
Manelli	I-PER
,	O
Robert	B-PER
Schiel	I-PER
	
George	B-PER
Frost	I-PER
Bloomer	I-PER
?	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
	
He	O
visited	O
Cuba	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
later	O
resided	O
in	O
Orange	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC
.	O
	
He	O
attended	O
Wilberforce	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
where	O
he	O
played	O
in	O
the	O
bands	O
of	O
Ernie	B-PER
Fields	I-PER
and	O
Tiny	B-PER
Bradshaw	I-PER
.	O
	
''	O
Shine	B-ORG
My	I-ORG
Shoes	I-ORG
''	O
	
He	O
has	O
traveled	O
extensively	O
in	O
the	O
Western	B-LOC
Ghats	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
Himalayas	B-LOC
.	O
	
PS	B-ORG
Business	I-ORG
Parks	I-ORG
(	O
)	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Bolivia	B-LOC
and	O
Peru	B-LOC
.	O
	
50th	B-ORG
Golden	I-ORG
Globe	I-ORG
Awards	I-ORG
nominees	I-ORG
	
Anna	B-ORG
Cohi	I-ORG
FornellGuide	I-ORG
:	O
Raquel	B-ORG
Garcia	I-ORG
Borreguero	I-ORG
	
Siliștea	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Brăila	I-LOC
	
Lạch	B-ORG
Tray	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
,	O
Hai	B-LOC
Phong	I-LOC
,	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
	
Portage	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mackinac	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Michigan	I-LOC
	
*1955	O
:	O
Gösta	B-PER
Hammarlund	I-PER
,	O
Dagbladet	B-ORG
''	O
	
Boris	B-PER
K.	I-PER
Schischkin	I-PER
	
Before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Germany	B-LOC
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Adam	B-PER
Duffy	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
The	B-ORG
Elders	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
band	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''	O
Karneval	B-ORG
''	O
,	O
Hirato	O
	
Kootenay	B-ORG
Ice	I-ORG
(	O
1	O
)	O
	
See	O
,	O
Houghton	B-PER
,	I-PER
Norris	I-PER
.	O
	
M.Tech	O
in	O
Computer	B-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG
(	O
CSE	O
)	O
-	O
2	O
years	O
[Approved	O
intake	O
-	O
18]	O
	
Geffen	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
,	O
Domo	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
	
Varghese	B-PER
Payyappilly	I-PER
Palakkappilly	I-PER
	
Meriden	B-ORG
Silverites	I-ORG
-	O
1902-1905	O
.	O
	
Edward	B-PER
A.	I-PER
Gisburne	I-PER
	
One	O
of	O
these	O
seats	O
was	O
Borg	B-LOC
in	O
Lofoten	B-LOC
.	O
	
Julie	B-PER
Delpy	I-PER
/	O
Daniel	B-PER
Brühl	I-PER
	
Luis	B-PER
de	I-PER
Morales	I-PER
	
**Runner-up	O
:	O
1926–27	B-LOC
,	O
1927–28	B-LOC
,	O
1933–34	B-LOC
	
Edward	B-PER
Everett	I-PER
Horton	I-PER
,	O
Patsy	B-PER
Ruth	I-PER
Miller	I-PER
	
After	O
commissioning	O
,	O
''Schlesien	O
''	O
was	O
assigned	O
to	O
the	O
I	B-ORG
Battle	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Spartan	B-ORG
South	I-ORG
Midlands	I-ORG
Division	I-ORG
One	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
:	O
	
He	O
died	O
on	O
12	O
February	O
1305	O
at	O
Amberley	B-LOC
.	O
	
number	O
2	O
or	O
5	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
Llanelli	B-LOC
.	O
	
Avondale	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
Arturo	B-PER
Estrada	I-PER
Hernández	I-PER
(	O
1925-	O
)	O
	
Lee	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Scotland	B-ORG
women	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
national	I-ORG
football	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
	
Qaghans	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Turkic	I-ORG
khaganates	I-ORG
	
Tom	B-PER
James	I-PER
(	I-PER
rugby	I-PER
player	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Berzosa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Bureba	I-LOC
	
T.	B-PER
M.	I-PER
Soundararajan	I-PER
,	O
P.	B-PER
Susheela	I-PER
,	O
L.	B-PER
R.	I-PER
Eswari	I-PER
	
Tony	B-PER
Parker	I-PER
(	O
17	O
)	O
	
Hacking	B-ORG
at	I-ORG
Random	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
2009	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''	O
Tinea	B-LOC
pallescentella	I-LOC
''	O
Stainton	O
,	O
1851	O
	
Mackay	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Idaho	I-LOC
	
West	B-LOC
Newton	I-LOC
:	O
8	O
miles	O
	
John	B-PER
Wilson	I-PER
Croker	I-PER
	
He	O
attended	O
the	O
Académie	B-ORG
Royale	I-ORG
des	I-ORG
Beaux-Arts	I-ORG
in	O
Brussels	B-LOC
from	O
1860	O
to	O
1867	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
professors	O
being	O
Jean-François	B-PER
Portaels	I-PER
.	O
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Haarlem	B-LOC
.	O
	
AAA	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
band	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
[See	O
:	O
Margaret	B-PER
Hughes	I-PER
;	O
Katherine	B-PER
Corey	I-PER
.	O
	
**	O
Lake	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
(	O
near	O
Woodbridge	B-LOC
)	O
	
City	B-ORG
Cemetery	I-ORG
2	I-ORG
Mass	I-ORG
Grave	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Clarin	B-ORG
Awards	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Communes	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Nièvre	I-LOC
department	I-LOC
	
Eat	B-ORG
Me	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Drink	I-ORG
Me	I-ORG
''	O
	
Rajinikanth	B-PER
,	O
Chiranjeevi	B-PER
,	O
Sripriya	B-PER
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Australia	B-LOC
.	O
	
Andaman	B-LOC
green	I-LOC
pigeon	I-LOC
	
Albert	B-PER
Costa	I-PER
''	O
(	O
First	O
Round	O
)	O
	
Gulf	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Ob	I-LOC
	
*97	O
–	O
Calvin	B-PER
Tiggle	I-PER
–	O
1998	O
	
Carlos	B-PER
Jurado	I-PER
(	O
2007	O
)	O
	
Randi	B-PER
Mayem	I-PER
Singer	I-PER
and	O
Rina	B-PER
Mimoun	I-PER
	
Michigan	B-LOC
-	O
Wisconsin	B-LOC
-	O
Illinois	B-LOC
-	O
Indiana	B-LOC
	
*Senator	O
Bill	B-PER
Nelson	I-PER
(	O
D-FL	O
)	O
	
Richard	B-PER
Calder	I-PER
(	I-PER
writer	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Commercial	B-ORG
Hotel	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Fort	I-ORG
Smith	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Arkansas	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Kärpät	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
-	O
Jokerit	B-ORG
4:2	O
(	O
3:2	O
,	O
3:2	O
,	O
2:5	O
,	O
2:1	O
,	O
1:2	O
,	O
2:1	O
)	O
	
*Joint	O
bid	O
from	O
Calgary	B-LOC
and	O
Edmonton	B-LOC
,	O
Alberta	B-LOC
;	O
	
Makin	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Whoopee	I-ORG
''	O
	
'	O
''	O
Stefanie	B-PER
Scott	I-PER
''	O
'	O
(	O
born	O
1996	O
)	O
	
Members	O
of	O
the	O
disbanding	O
Greenback	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
met	O
on	O
October	O
21	O
at	O
the	O
Grand	B-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Hotel	I-ORG
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
.	O
	
**	O
''	O
County	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Burgundy	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
–	O
Otto-William	B-PER
(	O
982–1026	O
)	O
	
It	O
lies	O
approximately	O
south-east	O
of	O
Czosnów	B-LOC
,	O
south-east	O
of	O
Nowy	B-LOC
Dwór	I-LOC
Mazowiecki	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
north-west	O
of	O
Warsaw	B-LOC
.	O
	
Bill	B-PER
Walker	I-PER
–	O
assigned	O
by	O
the	O
Boston	B-ORG
Celtics	I-ORG
on	O
November	O
21	O
,	O
2009	O
	
State	B-LOC
Capitol	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
North	I-LOC
Dakota	I-LOC
	
''	O
The	B-ORG
Root	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
All	I-ORG
Evil	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2008	O
)	O
	
Ice	B-ORG
cream	I-ORG
cake	I-ORG
	
Son	O
of	O
Amine	B-PER
Gemayel	I-PER
,	O
nephew	O
of	O
Bachir	B-PER
Gemayel	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Baník	B-ORG
Ostrava	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Pennsylvania	B-ORG
Route	I-ORG
50	I-ORG
	
Robert	B-PER
A.	I-PER
Borski	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
1877	B-ORG
FA	I-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
Final	I-ORG
	
Johannes	B-PER
Secundus	I-PER
,	O
Neo-Latin	B-ORG
poet	O
(	O
1511–1536	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Vicente	B-PER
Fernández	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Buenos	I-ORG
Aires	I-ORG
,	O
2001	O
	
The	O
Bishop	B-PER
of	I-PER
Durham	I-PER
thought	O
them	O
the	O
finest	O
ever	O
seen	O
.	O
	
Paul	B-PER
Tang	I-PER
(	O
2007	O
)	O
	
Orthophytum	B-LOC
compactum	I-LOC
''	O
L.B	O
.	O
	
Laurentien	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Quebec	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
	
''	O
Polystichum	B-LOC
acrostichoides	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Michx	O
.	O
	
Gem	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Flathead	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Montana	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
With	O
the	O
Transcaucasus	B-ORG
Front	I-ORG
5.45	O
.	O
	
BBC	B-ORG
(	O
Test	B-ORG
Match	I-ORG
Special	I-ORG
''	O
)	O
	
2000–01	B-LOC
Cymru	I-LOC
Alliance	I-LOC
	
1950	O
–	O
North	B-ORG
Launceston	I-ORG
	
*Oberstleutnant	O
Paul-Werner	B-PER
Hozzel	I-PER
,	O
25	O
December	O
1944	O
–	O
16	O
April	O
1945	O
	
He	O
died	O
in	O
Cheltenham	B-LOC
,	O
aged	O
53	O
.	O
	
Zaara	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Charlotte	B-PER
Aiken	I-PER
/	O
Josh	B-PER
Whidborne	I-PER
	
Novy	B-LOC
Urengoy	I-LOC
(	O
Novy	B-LOC
Urengoy	I-LOC
)	O
	
Ishpeming	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Marquette	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Meagan	B-PER
Duhamel	I-PER
/	O
Eric	B-PER
Radford	I-PER
	
Clark	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
South	I-LOC
Dakota	I-LOC
	
Paul	B-PER
Hollins	I-PER
(	O
now	O
with	O
Heart	B-ORG
and	O
owner	O
of	O
Blue	B-LOC
Revolution	I-LOC
)	O
	
Jack	B-PER
Reynolds	I-PER
(	I-PER
American	I-PER
football	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Gloria	B-PER
Ehret	I-PER
(	O
1	O
)	O
'	O
''	O
	
Sunrise	B-ORG
Athletic	I-ORG
Conference	I-ORG
	
''	O
'	O
''	O
Coccothrinax	B-LOC
trinitensis	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
'	O
''	O
Jana	B-PER
Novotná	I-PER
''	O
'	O
defeated	O
Martina	B-PER
Hingis	I-PER
6–2	O
,	O
6–2	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
only	O
in	O
Madagascar	B-LOC
.	O
	
===Stage	O
3	O
,	O
April	O
9	O
,	O
2008	O
:	O
Erandio	B-LOC
>	O
Viana	B-LOC
,	O
195	O
km===	O
	
:	O
:Runner-up	O
(	O
1	O
)	O
:	O
2005	B-LOC
	
George	B-PER
,	I-PER
Nelson	I-PER
(	O
2004	O
)	O
.	O
	
:	O
2014	B-ORG
:	O
Josh	B-PER
Green	I-PER
(	O
33	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Jared	B-PER
Donaldson	I-PER
''	O
'4–6	O
,	O
6–3	O
,	O
7–5	O
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Eastwood	B-LOC
,	O
Nottinghamshire	B-LOC
.	O
	
Tigre	B-PER
Uno	I-PER
defeated	O
Rockstar	B-PER
Spud	I-PER
	
Stringtown	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Fountain	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
Antonio	B-PER
Vojak	I-PER
(	O
Napoli	B-ORG
)	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Tanzania	B-LOC
.	O
	
Karrie	B-PER
Webb	I-PER
(	O
9	O
)	O
	
Wax	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
UK	I-ORG
band	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Silesian	B-ORG
Fantasy	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
	
William	B-PER
Penny	I-PER
Brookes	I-PER
	
Samwell	B-LOC
Cave	I-LOC
cricket	I-LOC
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
St.	B-LOC
,	O
Russia	B-LOC
.	O
	
:	O
Joe	B-PER
Pantalone	I-PER
-	O
3,251	O
	
He	O
attended	O
Syracuse	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
where	O
he	O
studied	O
composition	O
with	O
Ernst	B-PER
Bacon	I-PER
,	O
who	O
encouraged	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
direction	O
.	O
	
**	O
Meet	O
EH	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
S	I-ORG
policies	O
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Kings	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Strathclyde	I-ORG
	
3	O
-	O
Edgar	B-PER
Prado	I-PER
(	O
1998	O
,	O
2004	O
,	O
2015	O
)	O
	
Sir	B-PER
Robert	I-PER
Bird	I-PER
,	I-PER
2nd	I-PER
Baronet	I-PER
	
Nancy	B-LOC
in	I-LOC
London	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
1966	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Zoltán	B-PER
Gera	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Michel	B-PER
Foucault	I-PER
(	O
1926–1984	O
)	O
	
Ben	B-PER
Weider	I-PER
(	O
1923–2008	O
)	O
	
La	B-LOC
Crosse	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
	
===Moved	O
to	O
Eastern	B-ORG
Football	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
	
Athens	B-LOC
encounters	O
defeat	O
at	O
Megara	B-LOC
.	O
	
Ponca	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
,	O
Oklahoma	B-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
	
''Sardinia	O
''	O
Vell	B-ORG
.	I-ORG
=	O
Guettarda	B-LOC
''	O
	
University	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	O
Roswell	B-LOC
	
No-no	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
12	O
June	O
1879	O
in	O
Hobart	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Tasmania	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Milton	B-ORG
Keynes	I-ORG
Lions	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Institut	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
Ciències	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
l'Espai	I-ORG
	
Suresh	B-PER
Gopi	I-PER
,	O
Priya	B-PER
Raman	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
With	O
Bob	B-PER
Cooper	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Scott	B-PER
Glenn	I-PER
,	O
Kevin	B-PER
Kline	I-PER
,	O
Kevin	B-PER
Costner	I-PER
,	O
John	B-PER
Cleese	I-PER
,	O
Danny	B-PER
Glover	I-PER
,	O
Jeff	B-PER
Goldblum	I-PER
,	O
Brian	B-PER
Dennehy	I-PER
,	O
Rosanna	B-PER
Arquette	I-PER
,	O
Linda	B-PER
Hunt	I-PER
	
**	O
Work	O
Experience	O
with	O
Richard	B-PER
Wilkins	I-PER
.	O
	
**	O
Johnson	B-PER
N.	I-PER
Camden	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
,	O
from	O
January	O
25	O
,	O
1893	O
	
East	B-LOC
Welega	I-LOC
Zone	I-LOC
	
''	O
Catocala	B-LOC
nymphagoga	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Esper	O
,	O
1787	O
)	O
	
Tatem	B-LOC
Elementary	I-LOC
School	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Collingswood	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
NJ	I-LOC
	
Ohm	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
law	I-ORG
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Brazil	B-LOC
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Zulfahmi	B-PER
Khairuddin	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
1927	O
in	O
West	B-LOC
Chester	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC
.	O
	
The	O
original	O
terminus	O
was	O
at	O
Angaston	B-ORG
.	O
	
''	O
Entephria	B-LOC
cyanata	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Hübner	O
,	O
1809	O
)	O
	
Rheal	B-PER
Cormier	I-PER
(	O
1–5	O
)	O
	
For	O
higher	O
studies	O
,	O
one	O
has	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Narasapuram	B-LOC
.	O
	
Initially	O
,	O
the	O
band	O
featured	O
BJH	O
drummer	O
Mel	B-PER
Pritchard	I-PER
.	O
	
***	O
(	O
1	O
)	O
Carlos	B-PER
Barredo	I-PER
(	O
)	O
5h	O
37	O
'	O
00	O
''	O
(	O
2	O
)	O
Roman	B-PER
Kreuziger	I-PER
(	O
)	O
s.t	O
.	O
	
Sun	B-PER
Myung	I-PER
Moon	I-PER
	
He	O
also	O
attended	O
Lake	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
Community	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
.	O
	
Prime	B-PER
Minister	I-PER
of	I-PER
the	I-PER
United	I-PER
Kingdom	I-PER
	
Night	B-PER
and	I-PER
Day	I-PER
''	O
(	O
2001–2003	O
)	O
	
François-Jean	B-PER
de	I-PER
Mesnil-Durand	I-PER
	
Warren	B-PER
Hill	I-PER
(	I-PER
prisoner	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
1967	O
–	O
Lauren	B-PER
Bacall	I-PER
	
ISO	B-PER
metric	I-PER
screw	I-PER
thread	I-PER
	
Kelly	B-PER
Downs	I-PER
(	O
2–4	O
)	O
	
Mike	B-PER
Trainor	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1981	O
)	O
,	O
comedian	O
.	O
	
Confederation	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Public	I-ORG
Workers	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
Unions	I-ORG
	
Warren	B-PER
P.	I-PER
Knowles	I-PER
	
League	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Communists	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Yugoslavia	I-ORG
	
Permanent	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Arbitration	I-ORG
(	O
PCA	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Alexandre	B-PER
Burrows	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Jim	B-PER
Talent	I-PER
60.22	O
%	O
-	O
Bob	B-PER
Holden	I-PER
37.54	O
%	O
	
'	O
''	O
Victor	B-PER
Obinna	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Guatemala	B-LOC
.	O
	
Appropriation	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
No.	I-ORG
3	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
Act	I-ORG
2005	I-ORG
	
Chestnut-bellied	B-LOC
mountain	I-LOC
tanager	I-LOC
	
``	O
Do	B-ORG
n't	I-ORG
Call	I-ORG
Me	I-ORG
Baby	I-ORG
''	O
	
Halo	B-ORG
2	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Original	I-ORG
Soundtrack	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2004	O
)	O
	
Ron	B-PER
Hornaday	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
(	O
see	O
Fecal	B-ORG
transplant	I-ORG
)	O
.	O
	
Les	B-PER
Binkley	I-PER
(	O
G	O
)	O
	
In	O
1988	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
attachment	O
to	O
Sunday	B-ORG
Sequence	I-ORG
as	O
presenter	O
.	O
	
He	O
obtained	O
a	O
total	O
number	O
of	O
16	O
caps	B-PER
for	O
the	O
Kazakhstan	B-ORG
national	I-ORG
football	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
during	O
his	O
career	O
,	O
scoring	O
three	O
goals	O
.	O
	
It	O
is	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Norwich	I-LOC
.	O
	
:	O
Ashleigh	B-PER
Brewer	I-PER
(	O
2014–	O
)	O
	
''	O
Trichopteryx	B-LOC
carpinata	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Borkhausen	O
,	O
1794	O
)	O
	
''	O
Medius	B-LOC
brassi	I-LOC
''	O
Fibiger	O
,	O
2011	O
	
*12	O
June	O
-	O
The	O
Republic	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Ireland	I-ORG
celebrates	O
a	O
win	O
over	O
England	B-ORG
1–0	O
at	O
Euro	B-ORG
88	I-ORG
.	O
	
Bernhard	B-PER
Langer	I-PER
(	O
2	O
)	O
	
``	O
Livin	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Joy	I-ORG
''	O
	
)	O
;	O
''Yogavartika	O
''	O
of	O
Vijnanabhiksu	B-PER
(	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
century	O
C.E	O
.	O
	
''	O
In	B-PER
Living	I-PER
Color	I-PER
''	O
(	O
1993	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Pat	B-PER
Convery	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
promotion	O
,	O
final	O
against	O
U.R.S.	B-ORG
du	I-ORG
Centre	I-ORG
1–0	O
:	O
4:4	O
	
''Crockett	O
''	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Tacoma	B-ORG
Boatbuilding	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
,	O
Tacoma	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Washington	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
commissioned	O
24	O
June	O
1967	O
.	O
	
''	O
WWE	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
The	O
Kaunda	B-ORG
Family	O
''	O
'	O
	
L.	B-PER
Dana	I-PER
Wilgress	I-PER
	
Chris	B-PER
Jack	I-PER
,	O
3	O
.	O
	
It	O
is	O
known	O
from	O
Maharashtra	B-LOC
in	O
India	B-LOC
.	O
	
174	O
Cedar	B-LOC
Fort	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Utah	I-LOC
$	O
14,266	O
	
1980–81	B-ORG
Phoenix	I-ORG
Suns	I-ORG
season	I-ORG
	
Carmem	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
Oliveira	I-ORG
—	O
did	O
not	O
finish	O
(	O
→	O
no	O
ranking	O
)	O
	
John	B-PER
Cartwright	I-PER
(	I-PER
political	I-PER
reformer	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Carl	B-PER
Hooper	I-PER
(	O
WIN	O
)	O
,	O
233	O
	
America	B-ORG
Again	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Re-becoming	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Greatness	I-ORG
We	I-ORG
Never	I-ORG
Were	I-ORG
n't	I-ORG
''	O
	
Sultanate	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Lahej	I-LOC
	
Written	O
by	O
Ronnie	B-PER
Van	I-PER
Zant	I-PER
and	O
guitarist	O
Allen	B-PER
Collins	I-PER
,	O
it	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
1977	O
on	O
the	O
album	O
Street	B-ORG
Survivors	I-ORG
''	O
.	O
	
Alfonso	B-PER
Daniel	I-PER
Rodríguez	I-PER
Castelao	I-PER
	
Frequent	O
contributors	O
included	O
Fritz	B-PER
Leiber	I-PER
and	O
Gene	B-PER
Wolfe	I-PER
.	O
	
Hesperia	B-LOC
Unified	I-LOC
School	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
	
Mitch	B-PER
Brown	I-PER
(	O
2006-	O
)	O
	
Vaishali	B-ORG
metro	I-ORG
station	I-ORG
	
Seth	B-PER
Hastings	I-PER
(	O
F	O
)	O
	
''	O
Margaret	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
(	O
23	O
February	O
1416	O
–	O
20	O
May	O
1444	O
)	O
,	O
married	O
first	O
William	B-PER
III	I-PER
,	I-PER
Duke	I-PER
of	I-PER
Bavaria	I-PER
on	O
11	O
May	O
1433	O
,	O
second	O
Ulrich	B-PER
V	I-PER
,	I-PER
Count	I-PER
of	I-PER
Württemberg	I-PER
on	O
29	O
January	O
1441	O
	
Sleepy	B-PER
Brown	I-PER
,	O
Jazze	B-PER
Pha	I-PER
	
Before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Germany	B-LOC
.	O
	
They	O
took	O
place	O
in	O
Nagoya	B-LOC
from	O
November	O
23	O
through	O
24	O
,	O
2008	O
.	O
	
**	O
''	O
Legendary	B-ORG
Witches	I-ORG
''	O
	
She	O
is	O
first	O
seen	O
following	O
Harry	B-PER
Houdini	I-PER
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
A.	B-PER
Victor	I-PER
Donahey	I-PER
''	O
'	O
:	O
577,044	O
	
Tris	B-PER
Coffin	I-PER
appeared	O
in	O
this	O
episode	O
.	O
	
Bijapur	B-LOC
district	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Karnataka	I-LOC
	
**	O
''	O
Semi-finals	O
:	O
2013	B-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Gujranwala	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
*Municipal	O
Human	B-ORG
Development	I-ORG
Index	I-ORG
:	O
.650	O
(	O
2000	O
)	O
	
SO03	O
:	O
Bari	B-LOC
Region	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Somalia	I-LOC
	
William	B-PER
Croft	I-PER
(	I-PER
linguist	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
School	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Business	I-ORG
Administration	I-ORG
Turiba	I-ORG
	
''	O
Mach	B-ORG
5	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
3:15	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
South	I-LOC
Wales	I-LOC
,	O
Queensland	B-LOC
and	O
Western	B-LOC
Australia	I-LOC
.	O
	
''	O
'Manager	O
''	O
'-	O
Brian	B-PER
Reid	I-PER
	
It	O
is	O
known	O
from	O
Chile	B-LOC
.	O
	
McCoy	B-ORG
''	O
(	O
1975-1976	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Colin	B-PER
Edwards	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Tom	B-PER
Metzger	I-PER
-	O
76,502	O
(	O
2.78	O
%	O
)	O
	
It	O
is	O
located	O
within	O
Central	B-LOC
Province	I-LOC
.	O
	
``	O
Kelly	B-PER
Clarkson	I-PER
co-wrote	O
this	O
track	O
from	O
the	O
album	O
.	O
	
William	B-ORG
Paul	I-ORG
–	O
CD	B-ORG
Aves	I-ORG
–	O
2005–2007	O
	
Jakub	B-PER
Wilk	I-PER
(	O
2012	O
)	O
	
S.V.	B-ORG
Zulte	I-ORG
Waregem	I-ORG
	
Voorlezer	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
House	I-ORG
	
Cerveteri	B-LOC
,	O
1822	O
-	O
Turate	B-LOC
,	O
1900	O
	
Donald	B-PER
V.	I-PER
Fites	I-PER
,	O
Caterpillar	B-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
*Rep.	O
Cynthia	B-PER
Lummis	I-PER
(	O
R-WY	O
)	O
and	O
Rep.	O
Gwen	B-PER
Moore	I-PER
(	O
D-WI	O
)	O
,	O
2011–2013	O
	
Cávado	B-LOC
(	O
near	O
Esposende	B-LOC
)	O
	
Simon	B-PER
Kernick	I-PER
–	O
Relentless	B-ORG
''	O
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Hobart	I-ORG
Welded	I-ORG
Steel	I-ORG
House	I-ORG
Co.	I-ORG
houses	I-ORG
	
Andrew	B-PER
Price	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
	
The	B-ORG
Meltdown	I-ORG
with	I-ORG
Jonah	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Kumail	I-ORG
''	O
	
Pedro	B-PER
Girón	I-PER
Acuña	I-PER
Pacheco	I-PER
(	O
1445–1466	O
)	O
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Glasgow	B-LOC
,	O
Scotland	B-LOC
.	O
	
It	O
covers	O
the	O
stretch	O
between	O
Gothenburg	B-LOC
and	O
Karesuando	B-LOC
via	O
Trollhättan	B-LOC
,	O
Vänersborg	B-LOC
,	O
Mellerud	B-LOC
,	O
Åmål	B-LOC
,	O
Säffle	B-LOC
,	O
Grums	B-LOC
,	O
Sunne	B-LOC
,	O
Torsby	B-LOC
,	O
Stöllet	B-LOC
,	O
Malung	B-LOC
,	O
Mora	B-LOC
,	O
Sveg	B-LOC
,	O
Brunflo	B-LOC
,	O
Östersund	B-LOC
,	O
Strömsund	B-LOC
,	O
Dorotea	B-LOC
,	O
Vilhelmina	B-LOC
,	O
Storuman	B-LOC
,	O
Sorsele	B-LOC
,	O
Arvidsjaur	B-LOC
,	O
Jokkmokk	B-LOC
,	O
Gällivare	B-LOC
,	O
Svappavaara	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Vittangi	B-LOC
.	O
	
Trabzonspor	B-ORG
1–1	O
(	O
0–2	O
)	O
'	O
''	O
Benfica	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
.	O
	
Yvonne	B-PER
Strahovski	I-PER
–	O
Chuck	B-ORG
''	O
	
Killer	B-PER
Karl	I-PER
Kox	I-PER
	
He	O
is	O
the	O
cousin	O
of	O
Yoshimitsu	B-PER
Yamada	I-PER
.	O
	
The	B-ORG
Christmas	I-ORG
Song	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
EP	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O
	
:	O
:	O
''	O
Epacrocerus	B-LOC
''	O
,	O
Proepacrocerus	B-LOC
''	O
,	O
Tanymetopus	B-LOC
''	O
and	O
Udamolobium	B-LOC
''	O
.	O
	
Simon	B-PER
Williams	I-PER
(	I-PER
chess	I-PER
player	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Nick	B-PER
Jonas	I-PER
(	O
Island	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
)	O
-	O
Jealous	B-ORG
	
Ayame	B-PER
Goriki	I-PER
,	O
Kento	B-PER
Yamazaki	I-PER
	
''	O
Monochroa	B-LOC
lutulentella	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Zeller	O
,	O
1839	O
)	O
	
Gogeta	B-ORG
''	O
'2	O
''	O
'	O
	
It	O
is	O
known	O
from	O
New	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC
.	O
	
Nautical	B-ORG
Almanac	I-ORG
Office	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Villefranche	B-LOC
near	O
Nice	B-LOC
.	O
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
lakes	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Norway	I-ORG
	
Borja	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Zaragoza	I-LOC
	
Adrian	B-PER
Webster	I-PER
(	I-PER
footballer	I-PER
,	I-PER
born	I-PER
1980	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
''	O
Ischnobathra	B-LOC
dormiens	I-LOC
''	O
Meyrick	O
,	O
1937	O
	
Oberschönau	B-LOC
,	O
Thuringia	B-LOC
since	O
1992	O
	
Korean	B-ORG
Culture	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG
	
Mika	B-PER
Singh	I-PER
,	O
Hard	B-PER
Kaur	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Live	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
Carre	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
The	O
Long	B-ORG
Depression	I-ORG
hit	O
the	O
countryside	O
around	O
1874	O
,	O
forcing	O
farmers	O
to	O
reduce	O
their	O
output	O
or	O
sell	O
at	O
a	O
loss	O
.	O
	
(	O
m	B-ORG
/	O
w	B-ORG
)	O
	
Cecilia	B-PER
Victoria	I-PER
Strickland	I-PER
(	O
1897–1982	O
)	O
	
Federation	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Norwegian	I-ORG
Professional	I-ORG
Associations	I-ORG
	
Male	O
Vocalist	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
:	O
Corey	B-PER
Hart	I-PER
	
Scottish	B-PER
Gaelic	I-PER
literature	I-PER
	
Belize	B-LOC
District	I-LOC
:	O
13	O
(	O
including	O
10	O
in	O
Belize	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
)	O
	
Karjat	B-LOC
-	O
Pune	B-LOC
Passenger	O
.	O
	
Kevin	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
(	O
9	O
)	O
	
Grohotișul	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Bângăleasa	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
1982-1989	O
:	O
Ramón	B-PER
Búa	I-PER
Otero	I-PER
	
===Disc	O
twelve	O
:	O
Immortalis	B-ORG
''	O
===	O
	
He	O
started	O
his	O
career	O
in	O
Frigg	B-ORG
Oslo	I-ORG
FK	I-ORG
.	O
	
Nurullah	B-PER
Sağlam	I-PER
(	O
2009	O
)	O
	
Franz	B-PER
von	I-PER
Papen	I-PER
	
Chris	B-PER
Bosh	I-PER
,	O
Shawn	B-PER
Marion	I-PER
(	O
13	O
)	O
	
Turin	B-LOC
(	O
''Torino	O
''	O
)	O
	
William	B-PER
McKinley	I-PER
was	O
born	O
in	O
Niles	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ohio	I-LOC
,	O
in	O
1843	O
.	O
	
Lindeman	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
*16	O
/	O
10	O
/	O
99	O
Beck	B-PER
	
Religious	B-ORG
Studies	I-ORG
Review	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
Oct	O
2003	O
volume	O
29	O
,	O
page	O
353	O
.	O
	
*2004	O
:	O
Be	B-ORG
Here	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Keith	B-PER
Urban	I-PER
	
Chaves	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Mexico	I-LOC
	
Richard	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER
(	I-PER
British	I-PER
politician	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Luis	B-PER
Scola	I-PER
(	O
9	O
)	O
	
Hog	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Breath	I-ORG
Cafe	I-ORG
	
*1992	O
:	O
Arwut	B-ORG
Lub	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Secret	I-ORG
Weapons	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Pontedera	B-LOC
and	O
died	O
in	O
Florence	B-LOC
.	O
	
:	O
Zvolen	B-LOC
,	O
Slovakia	B-LOC
-	O
2007	O
	
Port	B-ORG
au	I-ORG
Prince	I-ORG
,	O
Haiti	B-LOC
	
President	B-ORG
:	O
José	B-PER
Eduardo	I-PER
dos	I-PER
Santos	I-PER
	
Charles	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Precourt	I-PER
Dominic	B-PER
L.	I-PER
Pudwill	I-PER
Gorie	I-PER
Wendy	B-PER
B.	I-PER
Lawrence	I-PER
Franklin	B-ORG
R.	I-ORG
Chang-Diaz	I-ORG
Janet	B-PER
L.	I-PER
Kavandi	I-PER
Valery	B-PER
Ryumin	I-PER
	
Workers	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
,	O
Beijing	B-LOC
	
Love	B-ORG
You	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''	O
New	B-ORG
Japan	I-ORG
Pro	I-ORG
Wrestling	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Yahn	B-LOC
|	O
Yazdan	B-LOC
Chah	I-LOC
|	O
Yegi	B-LOC
|	O
Yekkeh	B-LOC
Derakht	I-LOC
|	O
Yosht	B-LOC
|	O
Yusefabad	B-LOC
|	O
Yush	B-LOC
|	O
Yushu	B-LOC
	
Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Birmingham	I-LOC
in	I-LOC
Alabama	I-LOC
	
Bokówka	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Podlaskie	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC
	
Talebabad	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Gilan	I-LOC
	
Keni	B-PER
Thomas	I-PER
(	O
with	O
Emmylou	B-PER
Harris	I-PER
)	O
	
Lilly	B-ORG
Wood	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Prick	I-ORG
and	O
Robin	B-PER
Schulz	I-PER
	
Centre	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Economic	I-ORG
Policy	I-ORG
Research	I-ORG
	
Michael	B-PER
Anderson	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
Eureeka	B-PER
's	I-PER
Castle	I-PER
''	O
	
Annie	B-PER
and	I-PER
Clarabel	I-PER
	
Yancheng	B-LOC
as	O
of	O
July	O
2010	O
	
Panathinaikos	B-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
She	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Sanandaj	B-LOC
in	O
north-western	O
Iran	B-LOC
and	O
deceased	O
in	O
Sulaymaniyah	B-LOC
in	O
present-day	O
north-eastern	O
Iraq	B-LOC
.	O
	
Eric	B-PER
van	I-PER
de	I-PER
Poele	I-PER
Fermín	B-ORG
Velez	I-ORG
	
I	B-ORG
Bought	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Blue	I-ORG
Car	I-ORG
Today	I-ORG
	
:	O
Dave	B-PER
Otto	I-PER
,	O
DH	O
	
Memory]]	O
''	O
—	O
Andrew	B-PER
Lloyd	I-PER
Webber	I-PER
	
With	O
an	O
introduction	O
by	O
Lord	B-PER
Hailey	I-PER
.	O
	
Episcopal	B-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
	
Tazeh	B-LOC
Kand-e	I-LOC
Akhvond	I-LOC
	
The	O
Hebrew	B-ORG
inscriptions	O
found	O
on	O
Hasmonean	B-ORG
coins	O
are	O
:	O
	
San	B-ORG
Jose-Sunnyvale-Santa	I-ORG
Clara	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
CA	I-ORG
MSA	I-ORG
	
Irving	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
(	O
1905–1991	O
)	O
	
Antonio	B-PER
Sánchez	I-PER
de	I-PER
Bustamante	I-PER
y	I-PER
Sirven	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
'	O
''	O
Nikita	B-PER
Lobintsev	I-PER
(	O
1:45.10	O
)	O
Mikhail	B-PER
Polischuk	I-PER
(	O
1:45.42	O
)	O
Danila	B-PER
Izotov	I-PER
(	O
1:44.48	O
)	O
Alexander	B-PER
Sukhorukov	I-PER
(	O
1:44.15	O
)	O
	
He	O
has	O
also	O
played	O
for	O
Mumbai	B-ORG
Indians	I-ORG
.	O
	
Stapleton	B-PER
Cotton	I-PER
,	I-PER
1st	I-PER
Viscount	I-PER
Combermere	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
''Hatachi	O
''	O
'	O
''	O
is	O
the	O
debut	O
mini-album	O
released	O
by	O
duo	O
singers	O
Tackey	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Tsubasa	I-ORG
.	O
	
**2007	O
:	O
Mixtape	B-ORG
Messiah	I-ORG
3	I-ORG
''	O
	
**	O
''	O
The	B-ORG
Payback	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
James	B-PER
Brown	I-PER
	
It	O
consists	O
of	O
the	O
Bundesautobahn	B-ORG
3	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Bundesautobahn	B-ORG
4	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
Bundesautobahn	B-ORG
1	I-ORG
.	O
	
of	O
Oneida	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC
.	O
	
Landry	B-PER
Fields	I-PER
(	O
9	O
)	O
	
''	O
Pinus	B-LOC
halepensis	I-LOC
''	O
	
Spuyten	B-LOC
Duyvil	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Bronx	I-LOC
	
During	O
1979	O
and	O
1980	O
,	O
he	O
taught	O
at	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Maryland	I-ORG
,	O
then	O
at	O
Rhodes	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
.	O
	
In	O
2013	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
working	O
to	O
qualify	O
for	O
the	O
2016	B-ORG
Summer	I-ORG
Paralympics	I-ORG
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Zadie	B-PER
Smith	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Syd	B-PER
Walker	I-PER
,	O
Arthur	B-PER
Cleave	I-PER
	
Jubilee	B-ORG
Medal	I-ORG
``	I-ORG
In	I-ORG
Commemoration	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
100th	I-ORG
Anniversary	I-ORG
since	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Birth	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Vladimir	I-ORG
Il'ich	I-ORG
Lenin	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Ryan	B-PER
Day	I-PER
10	O
''	O
'–7	O
Drew	B-PER
Henry	I-PER
	
Marian	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Indiana	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Alan	B-PER
Alda	I-PER
,	O
Jacqueline	B-PER
Bisset	I-PER
,	O
Barbara	B-PER
Parkins	I-PER
	
Thom	B-PER
Wilson	I-PER
–	O
production	O
	
Syrian	B-LOC
Civil	I-LOC
War	I-LOC
	
Wayne	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Nebraska	I-LOC
	
It	O
succeeded	O
the	O
Old	B-ORG
Kingdom	I-ORG
Snefru	B-ORG
.	O
	
**	O
Robert	B-PER
Milkins	I-PER
8–	O
''	O
'23	O
Joe	B-PER
Swail	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Lingaraj	B-ORG
Temple	I-ORG
,	O
Bhubaneswar	B-LOC
34	O
	
Cass	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
(	O
northeast	O
)	O
	
Communist	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Ireland	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Marxist–Leninist	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''Bache	O
''	O
was	O
built	O
in	O
Wilmington	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Delaware	I-LOC
,	O
in	O
1871	O
.	O
	
Curd	B-PER
Jürgens	I-PER
...	O
Kaiser	B-PER
Franz	I-PER
Joseph	I-PER
von	I-PER
Österreich	I-PER
	
Max	B-PER
Jakob	I-PER
Friedländer	I-PER
	
Haruka	B-PER
Ayase	I-PER
,	O
Masaki	B-PER
Okada	I-PER
	
Beypazarı	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ankara	I-LOC
	
Warlord	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Star	I-ORG
Trek	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Voyager	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Robert	B-PER
De	I-PER
Niro	I-PER
,	O
Sean	B-PER
Penn	I-PER
,	O
Demi	B-PER
Moore	I-PER
	
Tennie	B-PER
Rogers	I-PER
–	O
12	O
(	O
0.00	O
%	O
)	O
	
The	O
founder	O
Mustafa	B-PER
Kemal	I-PER
Atatürk	I-PER
died	O
.	O
	
Amit	B-PER
Kumar	I-PER
,	O
Kavita	B-PER
Krishnamurthy	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Lou	B-PER
Pote	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Richard	B-PER
Berry	I-PER
Harrison	I-PER
	
Eldorado	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC
	
UIC	B-ORG
classification	I-ORG
:	O
'	O
''	O
1B2	O
''	O
'	O
(	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
German	B-ORG
classification	I-ORG
and	O
Italian	B-ORG
classification	I-ORG
)	O
	
Poppo]]	O
and	O
ending	O
the	O
Frisian	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC
.	O
	
1994	B-ORG
IAAF	I-ORG
World	I-ORG
Cross	I-ORG
Country	I-ORG
Championships	I-ORG
–	I-ORG
Junior	I-ORG
men	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
race	I-ORG
	
He	O
is	O
often	O
associated	O
with	O
Moses	B-PER
.	O
	
A	O
[[meander	O
on	O
the	O
River	B-LOC
Wharfe	I-LOC
between	O
Kettlewell	B-LOC
and	O
Starbotton	B-LOC
.	O
	
Royal	B-ORG
Australian	I-ORG
Corps	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Transport	I-ORG
-	O
The	B-ORG
Princess	I-ORG
Royal	I-ORG
	
Aziz	B-PER
Khan	I-PER
Mukri	I-PER
	
**	O
''	O
Orissa	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
:	O
Sambalpur	B-LOC
,	O
Anugul	B-ORG
,	O
Bargarh	B-LOC
,	O
Balangir	B-LOC
,	O
Debagarh	B-LOC
,	O
Dhenkanal	B-LOC
,	O
Jharsuguda	B-LOC
and	O
Sonapur	B-LOC
	
Àlex	B-PER
Corretja	I-PER
''	O
(	O
First	O
Round	O
)	O
	
Liechtenstein	B-LOC
follows	O
the	O
same	O
practice	O
.	O
	
It	O
was	O
named	O
after	O
the	O
Darwin	B-LOC
suburb	O
of	O
Stuart	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
.	O
	
''	O
Firme	B-ORG
''	O
–	O
1995	O
Epitaph	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
	
***	O
1–1	O
in	O
Porto	B-LOC
Alegre	I-LOC
	
Texas	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Highway	I-ORG
Spur	I-ORG
408	I-ORG
	
Murder	B-PER
of	I-PER
Nubia	I-PER
Barahona	I-PER
	
Joint	B-ORG
Task	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG
2	I-ORG
	
His	O
political	O
stance	O
was	O
criticized	O
for	O
a	O
comment	O
to	O
newspaper	O
Den	B-ORG
''	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
in	O
1999	O
:	O
	
April–December	O
2012	O
:	O
Vice	B-ORG
Admiral	I-ORG
Sir	B-PER
Philip	I-PER
Jones	I-PER
	
Stephen	B-ORG
Collins	I-ORG
as	O
Eric	B-ORG
Camden	I-ORG
	
2015	B-LOC
Thai	I-LOC
Premier	I-LOC
League	I-LOC
runners-up	O
	
IEEE	B-ORG
Alexander	I-ORG
Graham	I-ORG
Bell	I-ORG
Medal	I-ORG
,	O
1986	O
	
It	O
will	O
be	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Fairbank	B-LOC
neighbourhood	O
at	O
the	O
intersection	O
of	O
Dufferin	B-ORG
Street	I-ORG
and	O
Eglinton	B-ORG
Avenue	I-ORG
West	I-ORG
.	O
	
Jim	B-PER
Denomie	I-PER
,	O
artist	O
	
Jeremy	B-PER
Clarkson	I-PER
,	O
broadcaster	O
and	O
journalist	O
,	O
then	O
presenter	O
of	O
Top	B-ORG
Gear	I-ORG
''	O
.	O
	
Outline	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
biochemistry	I-LOC
	
Thunderbolts	B-PER
''	O
158-163	O
	
Bishopric	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Constance	I-ORG
	
Idrætsparken	B-ORG
,	O
Copenhagen	B-LOC
(	O
H	O
)	O
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
mayors	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Baltimore	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Maryland	I-ORG
	
Toktamış	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ceyhan	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Honda	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
List	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
metropolitan	I-LOC
areas	I-LOC
in	I-LOC
Sweden	I-LOC
	
2nd	B-ORG
Cavalry	I-ORG
Division	I-ORG
Emanuele	I-ORG
Filiberto	I-ORG
Testa	I-ORG
di	I-ORG
Ferro	I-ORG
	
The	O
first	O
Census	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
to	O
take	O
place	O
after	O
settlement	O
,	O
in	O
1901	O
,	O
recorded	O
the	O
population	O
as	O
46	O
.	O
	
Nigel	B-PER
Barley	I-PER
(	O
1984	O
)	O
	
Na	B-ORG
aana	I-ORG
is	I-ORG
des	I-ORG
laado	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Neželjene	O
)	O
''	O
	
Nakoda	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
Stoney	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Assistant	B-ORG
Secretary	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Navy	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Manpower	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Reserve	I-ORG
Affairs	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Two	O
years	O
later	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
offered	O
the	O
position	O
by	O
Theodore	B-PER
Roosevelt	I-PER
,	O
but	O
he	O
declined	O
.	O
	
''	O
Kim	B-PER
Jung-nan	I-PER
''	O
'	O
-	O
'	O
''	O
You	B-ORG
Are	I-ORG
My	I-ORG
Destiny	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
Co-	O
Written	O
and	O
Produced	O
by	O
Kim	B-PER
Fowley	I-PER
.	O
	
Stanisław	B-PER
Lem	I-PER
,	O
writer	O
,	O
born	O
in	O
Lviv	B-LOC
	
Philippine	B-LOC
forest	I-LOC
roundleaf	I-LOC
bat	I-LOC
,	O
''H	O
.	O
	
Accra	B-ORG
Sports	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
,	O
Accra	B-LOC
,	O
Ghana	B-LOC
	
Jellyfish	B-ORG
Entertainment	I-ORG
,	O
Avex	B-ORG
Taiwan	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Greer	B-PER
Garson	I-PER
''	O
'	O
‡	O
	
Live	B-LOC
at	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Fillmore	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
1994	O
)	O
	
Kek	B-ORG
Lok	I-ORG
Si	I-ORG
Temple	I-ORG
	
Mountain	B-LOC
Communities	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Tejon	I-LOC
Pass	I-LOC
	
''	O
Kara	B-ORG
Koyunlu	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Black	I-ORG
Sheep	I-ORG
Turkomans	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Qara	B-PER
Yusuf	I-PER
(	O
~1388	O
to	O
1399	O
/	O
1400	O
)	O
	
:	O
'	O
''	O
1956	O
''	O
'	O
La	B-ORG
Finestra	I-ORG
sul	I-ORG
Luna	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
	
Carlos	B-PER
Irizarry	I-PER
Yunqué	I-PER
	
Blood	B-ORG
on	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Tracks	I-ORG
''	O
	
``	B-ORG
Paparazzi	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Xzibit	I-ORG
song	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''	O
'Assistant	O
Coach	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
Larry	B-PER
Robinson	I-PER
(	O
Oct-Mar	O
)	O
	
The	B-ORG
Guardian	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
``	O
Doggin	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Around	I-ORG
''	O
	
''	O
Micropterix	B-LOC
tunbergella	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Fabricius	O
,	O
1787	O
)	O
	
Clarence	B-PER
R.	I-PER
Magney	I-PER
	
200	B-ORG
Motels	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1971	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Claude	B-PER
Chabrol	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
The	O
species	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC
.	O
	
James	B-PER
Roosevelt	I-PER
(	I-PER
1760–1847	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Jana	B-PER
Novotná	I-PER
(	O
2	O
)	O
Arantxa	B-PER
Sánchez	I-PER
Vicario	I-PER
	
Jean	B-PER
Carnahan	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
	
It	O
is	O
a	O
subrange	O
of	O
the	O
Prades	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
.	O
	
Hiroko	B-PER
Takenishi	I-PER
(	O
2012	O
)	O
,	O
author	O
.	O
	
**	O
Charles	B-PER
(	O
1336–1348	O
)	O
	
Tiger	B-PER
Woods	I-PER
:	O
1994	O
,	O
1995	O
,	O
1996	O
Amateurs	O
;	O
2000	O
,	O
2002	O
,	O
2008	O
Opens	O
	
Killed	B-PER
in	I-PER
action	I-PER
14	O
August	O
1944	O
	
FC	B-ORG
Issyk-Kol	I-ORG
Karakol	I-ORG
	
Kuurn	B-LOC
Kopan	I-LOC
Noot	I-LOC
language	I-LOC
	
Lahaina	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Hawaii	I-LOC
	
This	O
equalled	O
the	O
previous	O
record	O
of	O
ten	O
wins	O
set	O
by	O
Janet	B-PER
Morgan	I-PER
from	O
1950	O
through	O
to	O
1959	O
.	O
	
Moreno	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Rennell	I-LOC
Island	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Nick	B-PER
Rimando	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
Scott	B-PER
Pruett	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
*1924	O
–	O
Champagne	B-ORG
Bath	I-ORG
and	O
Plant	B-ORG
Bath	I-ORG
built	O
.	O
	
Supah	B-ORG
Ninjas	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2011-2013	O
)	O
	
[[Postcard	O
from	O
Fiskebäckskil	B-LOC
around	O
1900	O
.	O
	
How	B-ORG
to	I-ORG
Save	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG
''	O
	
Bulacan	B-ORG
Agricultural	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
	
Barney	B-PER
Frank	I-PER
(	O
D–Massachusetts	O
;	O
retired	O
in	O
2013	O
)	O
	
Víctor	B-PER
Valdés	I-PER
(	O
2	O
)	O
	
George	B-PER
R.	I-PER
Mather	I-PER
	
Witold	B-PER
Rudziński	I-PER
(	O
1913–2004	O
)	O
	
He	O
represented	O
Prince	B-LOC
Edward	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
Canadian	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Commons	I-ORG
from	O
1891	O
to	O
1896	O
as	O
a	O
Conservative	B-ORG
member	O
.	O
	
''	O
Chloroclystis	B-LOC
catastreptes	I-LOC
''	O
	
Santa	B-LOC
Marta	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
Penaguião	I-LOC
	
On	O
the	O
Aragvi	B-ORG
river	I-ORG
,	O
from	O
Tbilisi	B-LOC
	
;	O
Elliott	B-PER
Yamin	I-PER
-	O
Elliott	B-ORG
Yamin	I-ORG
''	O
	
Noah	B-PER
Beery	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
as	O
Sgt	O
.	O
	
``	O
U	B-ORG
Ca	I-ORG
n't	I-ORG
Touch	I-ORG
This	I-ORG
''	O
	
When	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
his	O
family	O
moved	O
to	O
White	B-LOC
Plains	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC
.	O
	
Wes	B-PER
Morgan	I-PER
-	O
January	O
2012	O
£1,000,000	O
	
It	O
is	O
located	O
on	O
Davis	B-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
.	O
	
*Episode	O
18	O
–	O
Ulrika	B-PER
Jonsson	I-PER
	
Leslie	B-PER
Nielsen	I-PER
,	O
Nicollette	B-PER
Sheridan	I-PER
,	O
Andy	B-PER
Griffith	I-PER
,	O
Barry	B-PER
Bostwick	I-PER
,	O
Marcia	B-PER
Gay	I-PER
Harden	I-PER
,	O
Charles	B-PER
Durning	I-PER
	
Baldwin	B-LOC
Hills	I-LOC
/	I-LOC
Crenshaw	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Los	I-LOC
Angeles	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
World	B-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
2014	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Newport	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
town	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
York	I-LOC
	
Republic	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Venice	I-LOC
	
Muzik]]	O
''	O
(	O
4Minute	B-ORG
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Monica	B-PER
Roșu	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
She	O
married	O
Gunnar	B-PER
Myrdal	I-PER
in	O
1924	O
.	O
	
Máximo]]	O
and	O
Volador	B-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
(	O
hair	O
)	O
	
Bradyrrhoa	B-LOC
confiniella	I-LOC
''	O
Zeller	O
,	O
1848	O
	
Uluçınar	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
İmamoğlu	I-LOC
	
Paul	B-PER
Drayson	I-PER
,	I-PER
Baron	I-PER
Drayson	I-PER
	
Tenerife	B-LOC
,	O
Canary	B-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
,	O
Spain	B-LOC
	
Nova	B-ORG
iznenađenja	I-ORG
za	I-ORG
nova	I-ORG
pokolenja	I-ORG
''	O
	
Both	O
countries	O
are	O
full	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
Central	B-ORG
European	I-ORG
Initiative	I-ORG
and	O
of	O
the	O
Southeast	B-ORG
European	I-ORG
Cooperative	I-ORG
Initiative	I-ORG
.	O
	
In	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
named	O
after	O
Mount	B-LOC
Atago	I-LOC
,	O
located	O
outside	O
Kyoto	B-LOC
.	O
	
Ahmad	B-PER
Hatifi	I-PER
-	O
Plays	O
for	O
Afghan	B-ORG
national	I-ORG
football	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
	
Carter	B-ORG
G.	I-ORG
Woodson	I-ORG
Home	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
Historic	I-ORG
Site	I-ORG
	
Abingdon	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
SpongeBob	B-ORG
SquarePants	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
season	I-ORG
7	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Brunei	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
Astrakhan	B-LOC
Oblast	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
ITV	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
Granada	I-ORG
Reports	I-ORG
	
''	O
Calamotropha	B-LOC
sienkiewiczi	I-LOC
''	O
Bleszynski	O
,	O
1961	O
	
Vasil	B-ORG
Levski	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
Military	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
Veliko	B-LOC
Tarnovo	I-LOC
	
It	O
is	O
known	O
from	O
South	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
.	O
	
''	O
Lacanobia	B-LOC
thalassina	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Hufnagel	O
,	O
1766	O
)	O
	
Villa	B-ORG
Nueva	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
John	B-PER
Aylesworth	I-PER
and	O
Frank	B-PER
Peppiatt	I-PER
(	O
Hee	B-PER
Haw	I-PER
''	O
)	O
produced	O
''Everything	O
Goes	O
''	O
.	O
	
David	B-PER
Nickson	I-PER
,	I-PER
Baron	I-PER
Nickson	I-PER
	
In	O
1929	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
working	O
as	O
a	O
freelance	O
writer	O
,	O
from	O
1929	O
to	O
1933	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Frankfurter	B-ORG
Zeitung	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
from	O
1932	O
to	O
1938	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Berliner	B-ORG
Tageblatt	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
from	O
1933	O
to	O
1934	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Vossische	B-ORG
Zeitung	I-ORG
''	O
.	O
	
Chimanlal	B-ORG
Girdharlal	I-ORG
Road	I-ORG
	
Wagoner	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Oklahoma	I-LOC
	
He	O
also	O
competed	O
in	O
the	O
two-man	B-ORG
event	I-ORG
but	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
finish	O
.	O
	
-	O
Piancastagnaio	B-LOC
(	O
SI	B-LOC
)	O
	
Buin	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Zanjan	I-LOC
	
''	O
Nauru	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
Meleagros	B-LOC
''	O
Kirschenhofer	O
,	O
1999	O
	
Berrien	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC
	
James	B-ORG
Louis	I-ORG
Jelinek	I-ORG
1993	O
-	O
2010	O
	
Bar-tailed	B-LOC
lark	I-LOC
,	O
''Ammomanes	O
cincturus	O
''	O
	
Two	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Half	I-ORG
Men	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
season	I-ORG
1	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Girard	B-LOC
Estate	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Philadelphia	I-LOC
	
:	O
Stephen	B-PER
Martines	I-PER
(	O
2003–2005	O
)	O
	
*1972	O
–	O
Elected	O
to	O
the	O
Serbian	B-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Sciences	I-ORG
	
Jean	B-PER
De	I-PER
Briac	I-PER
-	O
Shopkeeper	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Bolivia	B-LOC
and	O
Peru	B-LOC
.	O
	
Mikage	B-ORG
Station	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Hanshin	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Cadaqués	B-LOC
,	O
Cap	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Creus	I-LOC
	
José	B-PER
Manuel	I-PER
Zozaya	I-PER
	
''	O
Ayman	B-PER
Al	I-PER
Hagri	I-PER
''	O
'	O
–	O
Tractor	B-ORG
Sazi	I-ORG
–	O
2011	O
	
James	B-PER
Donald	I-PER
(	I-PER
politician	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
''all	O
songs	O
by	O
Paul	B-PER
Field	I-PER
''	O
	
Żebbuġ	B-ORG
Rangers	I-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Marco	B-PER
Melandri	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Bąków	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Przysucha	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Rupert	B-PER
Hamer	I-PER
,	O
LL.M.	O
,	O
MLC	O
	
La	B-ORG
Familia	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
rap	I-ORG
group	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Her	O
students	O
included	O
Robert	B-PER
Murray	I-PER
and	O
Allen	B-PER
Sapp	I-PER
.	O
	
''	O
December	O
27	O
''	O
–	O
Some	B-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
Required	I-ORG
	
The	O
paperback	O
edition	O
includes	O
a	O
foreword	O
by	O
Lawrence	B-PER
Lessig	I-PER
.	O
	
It	O
ultimately	O
ends	O
at	O
I-155	B-ORG
/	O
US	B-ORG
412	I-ORG
.	O
	
He	O
participated	O
in	O
three	O
Winter	B-ORG
Olympics	I-ORG
.	O
	
NUTS	B-LOC
codes	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Czech	I-LOC
Republic	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
Construction	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Brady	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
	
Ferrières-en-Bray	B-LOC
(	O
76260	O
)	O
	
Lew	B-ORG
Alcindor	I-ORG
(	O
37.2	O
)	O
	
Tazewell	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
:	O
Illinois	B-LOC
;	O
Virginia	B-LOC
	
Nishidai	B-ORG
Station	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Hyogo	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
``	O
Your	B-ORG
Love	I-ORG
Is	I-ORG
My	I-ORG
Drug	I-ORG
''	O
	
Eugenijus	B-PER
Maldeikis	I-PER
''	O
from	O
18	O
May	O
2006	O
''	O
	
2003	O
:	O
A.	B-PER
Richard	I-PER
Newton	I-PER
	
Art	B-ORG
n	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
Soul	I-ORG
—	O
``	O
Ever	B-ORG
Since	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
Went	I-ORG
Away	I-ORG
''	O
	
He	O
currently	O
owns	O
his	O
own	O
firm	O
,	O
based	O
in	O
Cork	B-LOC
.	O
	
Tow	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Town	I-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
Saybrook	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ashtabula	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ohio	I-LOC
	
Jakub	B-PER
Polak	I-PER
(	I-PER
musician	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Ali	B-PER
Thani	I-PER
Jumaa	I-PER
	
Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Alessandria	I-LOC
	
3PBS	B-ORG
-	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
,	O
Australia	B-LOC
-	O
http	O
:	O
/	O
/	O
www.pbsfm.org.au	O
/	O
	
'	O
''	O
Trois	B-ORG
Hommes	I-ORG
à	I-ORG
Abattre	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
Radstone	B-LOC
,	O
Roade	B-LOC
,	O
Rothersthorpe	B-LOC
	
Alfred	B-PER
Körte	I-PER
and	O
Gustav	B-PER
Körte	I-PER
:	O
discovered	O
Gordium	B-LOC
,	O
1900	O
	
Martin	B-PER
Luther	I-PER
King	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
Constantine	B-PER
VIII	I-PER
(	O
1025–1028	O
)	O
	
Governor	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Georgia	I-ORG
:	O
David	B-PER
Brydie	I-PER
Mitchell	I-PER
(	O
Democratic-Republican	B-ORG
)	O
(	O
until	O
November	O
5	O
)	O
,	O
Peter	B-PER
Early	I-PER
(	O
Democratic-Republican	B-ORG
)	O
(	O
starting	O
November	O
5	O
)	O
	
Jacob	B-PER
K.	I-PER
Olupona	I-PER
	
Argentina	B-LOC
,	O
Uruguay	B-LOC
,	O
Venezuela	B-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
	
With	O
an	O
Appendix	O
by	O
Solomon	B-PER
Feferman	I-PER
.	O
	
''	O
Zeiraphera	B-LOC
griseana	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Hübner	O
,	O
1799	O
)	O
	
He	O
moved	O
to	O
Alma	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC
in	O
1855	O
.	O
	
===	O
Corps	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
Ballet	I-ORG
===	O
	
Japanese	B-LOC
shrew	I-LOC
mole	I-LOC
	
2006–07	B-LOC
NFL	I-LOC
playoffs	I-LOC
	
*Jackling	O
,	O
West	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
	
Bill	B-PER
George	I-PER
(	I-PER
dog	I-PER
dealer	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Mr.	B-ORG
Blue	I-ORG
Sky	I-ORG
-	O
Written	O
and	O
Performed	O
by	O
Jeff	B-PER
Lynne	I-PER
	
Moby	B-PER
—	O
``	O
In	B-ORG
My	I-ORG
Heart	I-ORG
''	O
/	O
Bodyrock	B-ORG
	
''	O
Pareclectis	B-LOC
invita	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Meyrick	O
,	O
1912	O
)	O
	
The	O
song	O
``	O
What	B-ORG
Have	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
Done	I-ORG
''	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
single	O
released	O
from	O
the	O
album	O
.	O
	
Oakville]]	O
,	O
Ontario	B-LOC
Sept.	O
6-9	O
	
*1929	O
:	O
Ettore	B-PER
Tavernari	I-PER
(	O
3	O
)	O
	
Kirby	B-ORG
:	I-ORG
Right	I-ORG
Back	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
Ya	I-ORG
!	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
June	O
6	O
,	O
2009	O
–	O
July	O
11	O
,	O
2009	O
)	O
	
''	O
League	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Ireland	I-ORG
(	O
1	O
)	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
	
112	O
,	O
105	O
Nick	B-PER
Pearce	I-PER
	
Greg	B-PER
Monroe	I-PER
(	O
32	O
)	O
	
Daria	B-PER
Popova	I-PER
/	O
Bruno	B-PER
Massot	I-PER
Vanessa	B-PER
James	I-PER
/	O
Morgan	B-PER
Ciprès	I-PER
	
FedEx	B-ORG
used	O
to	O
operate	O
a	O
freight	O
facility	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
	
Casgrain	B-PER
,	I-PER
Henri-Raymond	I-PER
(	O
1895	O
)	O
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Kateryna	B-PER
Bondarenko	I-PER
(	O
Qualified	O
)	O
'	O
''	O
	
First	B-ORG
Congregational	I-ORG
Church	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Atlanta	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Georgia	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
He	O
was	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Salineville	B-ORG
American	B-ORG
Legion	I-ORG
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
KK	B-ORG
Sonik-Puntamika	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
'	O
''	O
'	O
''	O
(	O
France	B-LOC
)	O
''	O
	
He	O
died	O
on	O
9	O
May	O
1975	O
at	O
Hernstein	B-LOC
,	O
Austria	B-LOC
.	O
	
''	O
Pouzauges	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
*April	O
22	O
–	O
Marshall	B-PER
Riddle	I-PER
	
Debendranath	B-PER
Tagore	I-PER
,	O
(	O
1817–1905	O
)	O
	
A	O
member	O
of	O
Bellerophinidae	B-LOC
.	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
on	O
Cuba	B-LOC
.	O
	
''	O
Bidar	B-LOC
Sultanate	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
–	O
Qasim	B-ORG
Barid	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
(	O
1492–1504	O
)	O
	
A	O
further	O
four	O
decisions	O
were	O
implemented	O
,	O
aimed	O
at	O
striking	O
the	O
a	O
stable	O
racial	O
balance	O
among	O
the	O
troops	O
in	O
French	B-LOC
Indochina	I-LOC
.	O
	
Jenny	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Marguerite	I-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
image	O
:	O
Ζάν	O
Jean	B-PER
Cocteau	I-PER
	
12	O
:	O
Charlie	B-PER
Francis	I-PER
	
He	O
was	O
trained	O
in	O
Human	B-ORG
Rights	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
at	O
the	O
International	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Human	I-ORG
Rights	I-ORG
in	O
Strasbourg	B-LOC
(	O
1983	O
)	O
.	O
	
Regional	B-LOC
District	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Fraser-Cheam	I-LOC
	
Richard	B-PER
P.	I-PER
Bland	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
	
Terry	B-PER
Adams	I-PER
,	O
P	O
,	O
1995–1999	O
	
Chandigarh	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Architecture	I-ORG
,	O
Chandigarh	B-LOC
	
She	O
was	O
overhauled	O
at	O
Kure	B-ORG
Naval	I-ORG
Arsenal	I-ORG
from	O
4–29	O
July	O
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Current	O
''	O
Freddie	B-PER
M.	I-PER
Garcia	I-PER
(	O
1–	O
)	O
Vice	B-PER
Ganda	I-PER
(	O
5–	O
)	O
Angel	B-PER
Locsin	I-PER
(	O
5–	O
)	O
Robin	B-PER
Padilla	I-PER
(	O
5–	O
)	O
	
Mami	B-PER
Koyama	I-PER
,	O
Tōru	B-PER
Furuya	I-PER
,	O
Toshiko	B-PER
Fujita	I-PER
,	O
Chiyoko	B-PER
Kawashima	I-PER
	
Target	B-ORG
(	O
opened	O
in	O
1985	O
)	O
(	O
100,750	O
sq	O
ft	O
.	O
)	O
	
Svay	B-LOC
Rieng	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
town	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
''	O
Gorgonidia	B-LOC
cubotaensis	I-LOC
''	O
	
2247	O
)	O
,	O
in	O
Rome	B-LOC
.	O
	
Internal	B-ORG
Revenue	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG
	
Jisshu	B-PER
Sengupta	I-PER
,	O
Parambrato	B-ORG
Chatterjee	I-ORG
	
2010	B-ORG
AFF	I-ORG
Suzuki	I-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
qualification	I-ORG
	
Dreikurs	B-PER
,	I-PER
Rudolf	I-PER
(	O
1983	O
)	O
.	O
	
Common	B-LOC
greenshank	I-LOC
,	O
''Tringa	O
nebularia	O
''	O
	
:	O
John	B-PER
'Sammy	I-PER
'	I-PER
Newman	I-PER
(	O
2002	O
)	O
	
Sociobiological	B-PER
theories	I-PER
of	I-PER
rape	I-PER
	
Before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Germany	B-LOC
.	O
	
1773	O
:	O
Carl	B-PER
Stenborg	I-PER
	
''Slavonija	O
''	O
:	O
Slavonia	B-LOC
	
Ratan	B-PER
Kumar	I-PER
Sinha	I-PER
	
Léon	B-PER
Flament	I-PER
,	O
François	B-PER
de	I-PER
Coninck	I-PER
	
Its	O
remnants	O
were	O
demolished	O
in	O
1953	O
while	O
part	O
of	O
Kaliningrad	B-LOC
,	O
Russia	B-LOC
.	O
	
The	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
South	B-LOC
Holland	I-LOC
until	O
then	O
.	O
	
*14	O
/	O
11	O
/	O
87	O
Coldcut	B-ORG
	
2012-2013	O
-	O
Dulce	B-ORG
Amor	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Bristol	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
2	O
-	O
Tiznow	B-PER
(	O
2000	O
,	O
2001	O
)	O
	
Kootenay	B-ORG
Ice	I-ORG
''	O
'x	O
''	O
'	O
	
USL	B-ORG
Premier	I-ORG
Development	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
	
Magdalena	B-PER
Fręch	I-PER
Lyudmyla	B-PER
Kichenok	I-PER
Aleksandra	B-PER
Wozniak	I-PER
Emily	B-PER
Webley-Smith	I-PER
	
Dotted	B-LOC
garden	I-LOC
eel	I-LOC
	
Members	B-ORG
elected	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
2nd	I-ORG
Scottish	I-ORG
Parliament	I-ORG
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Peru	B-LOC
.	O
	
CSI	B-ORG
:	I-ORG
Crime	I-ORG
Scene	I-ORG
Investigation	I-ORG
''	O
	
Kenny	B-PER
de	I-PER
Schepper	I-PER
''	O
(	O
First	O
round	O
)	O
	
A	O
Warner	B-ORG
Bros	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
Production	O
.	O
	
Hwang	B-PER
Woo-yea	I-PER
(	O
May	O
15	O
,	O
2012	O
-	O
May	O
15	O
,	O
2014	O
)	O
	
'	O
''	O
Ján	B-PER
Kadár	I-PER
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
*January	O
23	O
–	O
Farmer	B-PER
Weaver	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
John	B-ORG
H.	I-ORG
Sturdy	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Yviers	B-LOC
(	O
16424	O
)	O
	
Malcolm	B-PER
C.	I-PER
Tarver	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
	
He	O
was	O
educated	O
at	O
the	O
Community	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Tehran	I-ORG
and	O
then	O
Carlisle	B-ORG
Technical	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
.	O
	
2010–11	B-LOC
Lebanese	I-LOC
Premier	I-LOC
League	I-LOC
runners-up	O
	
In	O
2000	O
,	O
she	O
duetted	O
with	O
Al	B-PER
Green	I-PER
on	O
``	O
Put	O
It	O
On	O
Paper	O
''	O
.	O
	
Ramsey	B-LOC
Public	I-LOC
School	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
	
New	B-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC
(	O
2014	O
)	O
	
1970]]	O
(	O
Chris	B-PER
Oddleifson	I-PER
)	O
	
Villages	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Vlorë	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
1966	O
in	O
Renton	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Washington	I-LOC
.	O
	
Hicham	B-PER
Arazi	I-PER
''	O
(	O
Second	O
Round	O
)	O
	
During	O
August	O
2012	O
,	O
only	O
parts	O
of	O
South	B-LOC
America	I-LOC
and	O
Northern	B-LOC
Australia	I-LOC
experienced	O
temperatures	O
that	O
were	O
cooler	O
than	O
usual	O
.	O
	
border	O
'	O
''	O
Séamus	B-PER
Harnedy	I-PER
	
Richard	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Daley	I-PER
-	O
2	O
(	O
0.07	O
%	O
)	O
	
*Maj	O
Franz	B-PER
Götz	I-PER
,	O
28	O
January	O
1945	O
–	O
7	O
May	O
1945	O
	
'	O
''	O
Rod	B-PER
Laver	I-PER
''	O
'	O
defeated	O
John	B-PER
Newcombe	I-PER
6–3	O
,	O
6–3	O
	
Saint	B-PER
Anne	I-PER
(	O
1805	O
)	O
	
1764	O
–	O
Exeter	B-ORG
Synagogue	I-ORG
consecrated	O
.	O
	
George	B-PER
Hill	I-PER
(	I-PER
figure	I-PER
skater	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Graham	B-PER
Fitkin	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1963	O
)	O
	
Arcada	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Gratiot	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
1897–98	B-ORG
Manchester	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
F.C.	I-ORG
season	I-ORG
	
Tihul	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Răstolița	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
Kleinbrook	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Texas	I-ORG
	
*29	O
March	O
–	O
Cantonales	B-ORG
Elections	I-ORG
held	O
.	O
	
1984	O
Who	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Zoomin	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
Who	B-ORG
?	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
Aretha	B-PER
Franklin	I-PER
	
Błotnica	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Greater	I-LOC
Poland	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC
	
1991–1996	O
3.8	O
L	O
(	O
231	O
in³	O
)	O
V6	B-ORG
	
Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Archdiocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Anqing	I-LOC
	
Through	O
his	O
mother	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cousin	O
of	O
William	B-PER
Carey	I-PER
who	O
was	O
the	O
brother-in-law	O
to	O
Anne	B-PER
Boleyn	I-PER
.	O
	
Bourke-White	B-PER
,	I-PER
Margaret	I-PER
.	O
	
SV	B-ORG
Zulte	I-ORG
Waregem	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
women	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
''	O
Juan	B-PER
Marichal	I-PER
''	O
'	O
,	O
P	O
,	O
1975	O
	
Florești	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mehedinți	I-LOC
	
Aura	B-LOC
an	I-LOC
der	I-LOC
Saale	I-LOC
	
**	O
U.S.	B-ORG
Diplomatic	I-ORG
Security	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG
(	O
DOS-DSS	O
)	O
	
Tan	B-PER
Aik	I-PER
Quan	I-PER
/	O
Lai	B-PER
Pei	I-PER
Jing	I-PER
	
Caio	B-PER
Zampieri	I-PER
,	O
6–3	O
,	O
6–2	O
	
He	O
died	O
in	O
July	O
of	O
1969	O
in	O
Williamsport	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC
.	O
	
The	O
species	O
resembles	O
Lecithocera	B-LOC
aulias	I-LOC
''	O
.	O
	
China	B-ORG
at	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Olympics	I-ORG
	
Mitchel	B-ORG
Field	I-ORG
,	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
,	O
November	O
1919	O
	
In	O
1996	O
-	O
2005	O
he	O
played	O
for	O
FC	B-ORG
Baník	I-ORG
Ostrava	I-ORG
.	O
	
Boško	B-PER
Janković	I-PER
(	O
26	O
/	O
12	O
)	O
	
Udinese	B-ORG
1–2	O
(	O
0–1	O
)	O
'	O
''	O
Arsenal	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
.	O
	
It	O
was	O
described	O
by	O
Moore	B-PER
in	O
1888	O
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
Shenyang	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
	
A2	B-ORG
motorway	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Portugal	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
South	B-ORG
Yorkshire	I-ORG
Passenger	I-ORG
Transport	I-ORG
Executive	I-ORG
	
IMRO	B-ORG
–	I-ORG
Bulgarian	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
Movement	I-ORG
	
William	B-PER
Roberts	I-PER
(	I-PER
footballer	I-PER
,	I-PER
born	I-PER
1907	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Na	B-ORG
h-Eileanan	I-ORG
Siar	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Casper	B-ORG
R.	I-ORG
Taylor	I-ORG
Jr	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
He	O
hailed	O
from	O
Søgne	B-LOC
.	O
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Brunei	B-LOC
,	O
India	B-LOC
(	O
the	O
Andamans	B-ORG
)	O
,	O
Indonesia	B-LOC
(	O
Sumatra	B-LOC
)	O
and	O
Malaysia	B-LOC
.	O
	
*Highest	O
transfer	O
fee	O
received	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
£2	O
million	O
''	O
'	O
–	O
Des	B-PER
Hamilton	I-PER
,	O
to	O
Newcastle	B-ORG
United	I-ORG
,	O
March	O
1997	O
.	O
	
''	O
Hellinsia	B-LOC
wrangeliensis	I-LOC
''	O
	
It	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
Saare	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
.	O
	
'	O
''	O
With	O
John	B-PER
Jenkins	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
:	O
:1st	O
Stage	O
3	O
,	O
David	B-PER
Bernabeu	I-PER
	
Galle	B-LOC
International	I-LOC
Stadium	I-LOC
,	O
Galle	B-LOC
	
Króle	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Masovian	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC
	
*1969	O
:	O
Polowanie	B-ORG
na	I-ORG
muchy	I-ORG
''	O
	
'	O
''	O
Rubén	B-PER
Xaus	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
TH54	O
:	O
Samut	B-LOC
Songkhram	I-LOC
Province	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Thailand	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
John	B-PER
Kocinski	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
350th	B-ORG
Fighter	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
(	O
LH	O
)	O
	
''	O
Senden	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
in	O
North	B-ORG
Rhine	I-ORG
Westphalia	I-ORG
.	O
	
16	O
Greg	B-PER
Biffle	I-PER
	
57th	B-ORG
Infantry	I-ORG
Regiment	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Ottoman	I-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Rapture	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Mavis	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
album	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Richard	B-PER
Hannon	I-PER
,	I-PER
Sr	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
Grand	B-ORG
Theater	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Salem	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Oregon	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
It	O
corresponded	O
to	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Saint-Léonard	B-ORG
neighbourhood	O
in	O
Montreal	B-LOC
.	O
	
Leventochori	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Elis	I-LOC
	
Kim	B-PER
Dong-hae	I-PER
(	O
129	O
Apps	O
,	O
1989–95*	O
)	O
	
SPD	B-ORG
21,9	O
%	O
(	O
+0,4	O
)	O
-	O
9	O
Seats	O
(	O
=	O
)	O
	
1996	O
-	O
2002	O
KPLR-TV	B-ORG
	
Rodrigo	B-PER
Kenton	I-PER
(	O
1992	O
)	O
	
Verizon	B-ORG
Theatre	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
Grand	I-ORG
Prairie	I-ORG
	
''	O
Ephestia	B-ORG
kuehniella	I-ORG
''	O
Zeller	O
,	O
1879	O
	
Exton	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Somerset	I-LOC
	
He	O
died	O
in	O
Gamburg	B-ORG
on	O
22	O
July	O
1902	O
.	O
	
Rupert	B-PER
Keegan	I-PER
took	O
the	O
B.A.R.C	O
.	O
	
In	O
2009	O
debuted	O
at	O
the	O
Palmeiras	B-ORG
B	I-ORG
.	O
	
Hell	B-ORG
Is	I-ORG
Sold	I-ORG
Out	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1951	O
)	O
	
Eagleville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Yuba	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
	
It	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Carroll	B-PER
Baker	I-PER
who	O
was	O
his	O
fellow	O
student	O
and	O
whom	O
he	O
married	O
.	O
	
East	B-LOC
Pakistan	I-LOC
(	O
now	O
Bangladesh	B-LOC
)	O
	
''	O
Belenois	B-LOC
aurota	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Fabricius	O
,	O
1793	O
)	O
	
Eric	B-PER
Pettigrew	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O
-	O
Incumbent	O
	
Christ	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
King	I-ORG
in	O
Świebodzin	B-LOC
,	O
Poland	B-LOC
	
*2008	O
–	O
``	O
All	B-ORG
Summer	I-ORG
Long	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
Kid	B-PER
Rock	I-PER
	
Jacques	B-PER
Pierre	I-PER
Abbatucci	I-PER
(	I-PER
minister	I-PER
)	I-PER
(	O
1791-1857	O
)	O
	
George	B-PER
MacDonald	I-PER
–	O
The	B-ORG
Princess	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Curdie	I-ORG
''	O
	
He	O
had	O
a	O
further	O
10-wicket	O
match	O
in	O
1907	O
against	O
Worcestershire	B-ORG
,	O
with	O
figures	O
of	O
six	O
for	O
43	O
and	O
four	O
for	O
88	O
.	O
	
Paul	B-PER
Robert	I-PER
Magocsi	I-PER
	
A	O
part	O
of	O
White	B-LOC
Mountain	I-LOC
National	I-LOC
Forest	I-LOC
.	O
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
constituencies	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Andhra	I-ORG
Pradesh	I-ORG
Vidhan	I-ORG
Sabha	I-ORG
	
When	O
1998	O
's	O
Ft.	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
''	O
failed	O
to	O
meet	O
those	O
expectations	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
band	O
left	O
for	O
full-time	O
jobs	O
or	O
more	O
commercially	O
successful	O
endeavors	O
.	O
	
Birgitta	B-PER
Lillpers	I-PER
,	O
poet	O
.	O
	
Hiroki	B-PER
Moriya	I-PER
,	O
6–3	O
,	O
6–2	O
	
Juventud	B-ORG
Unida	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
San	I-ORG
Miguel	I-ORG
	
Union	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Patriotic	I-LOC
Youth	I-LOC
	
*162	O
)	O
Homeacre-Lyndora	B-LOC
''pop	O
.	O
	
Scurria	B-LOC
scurra	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Lesson	O
,	O
1841	O
)	O
	
Volcanoes	B-LOC
National	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
Rwanda	B-LOC
	
Harry	B-LOC
Potter	I-LOC
and	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Half-Blood	I-LOC
Prince	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
16	O
July	O
2005	O
)	O
	
The	B-ORG
Kardomah	I-ORG
Gang	I-ORG
	
Governor	B-PER
of	I-PER
Massachusetts	I-PER
	
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
national	I-ORG
rugby	I-ORG
union	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
sevens	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Józefowo	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ostrołęka	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Fernando	B-PER
Lopes	I-PER
(	I-PER
filmmaker	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Passion	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Pain	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Pleasure	I-ORG
''	O
by	O
Trey	B-PER
Songz	I-PER
	
'	O
''	O
Canadian	B-ORG
Pacific	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Kosal	B-ORG
region	I-ORG
,	O
Western	B-LOC
Odisha	I-LOC
	
Colin	B-PER
Charvis	I-PER
(	O
capt	O
.	O
	
It	O
is	O
highly	O
preferred	O
in	O
Assam	B-LOC
and	O
locally	O
known	O
as	O
''singhi	O
''	O
.	O
	
Ian	B-PER
Hendry	I-PER
,	O
Alan	B-PER
Badel	I-PER
,	O
Barbara	B-PER
Ferris	I-PER
	
Kubra	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Najmeddin	I-ORG
(	O
1145–1220	O
)	O
	
Habib	B-PER
Ali	I-PER
al-Jifri	I-PER
	
Land	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Wealth	I-ORG
''	O
滙通天下	O
	
American	B-ORG
military	I-ORG
action	I-ORG
against	I-ORG
Iran	I-ORG
	
Cortina	B-LOC
Indian	I-LOC
Rancheria	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
	
'	O
''	O
HK	B-ORG
Dukla	I-ORG
Trenčín	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Shlomo	B-PER
Aviner	I-PER
(	O
1943-	O
)	O
	
Invasion	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Umuahia	I-ORG
	
William	B-PER
S.	I-PER
Hutchings	I-PER
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
stars	I-ORG
by	I-ORG
constellation	I-ORG
	
''	O
Watsonalla	B-LOC
cultraria	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Fabricius	O
,	O
1775	O
)	O
	
Tiffany	B-PER
Dupont	I-PER
,	O
Omar	B-PER
Sharif	I-PER
,	O
Peter	B-PER
O'Toole	I-PER
,	O
John	B-PER
Rhys-Davies	I-PER
,	O
Luke	B-PER
Goss	I-PER
	
1653	O
-	O
State	B-ORG
opera	I-ORG
active	O
.	O
	
Saab	B-PER
Magalona	I-PER
(	O
2016–present	O
)	O
	
Poalei	B-ORG
Agudat	I-ORG
Yisrael	I-ORG
:	O
2	O
	
Interstate	B-ORG
110	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
Route	I-ORG
110	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
California	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Sheila	B-PER
Copps	I-PER
(	O
L	O
)	O
9734	O
	
'	O
''	O
Lorde	B-PER
–	O
``	O
Royals	B-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O
	
Bill	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER
(	I-PER
footballer	I-PER
,	I-PER
born	I-PER
1869	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Gastrotheca	B-ORG
walkeri	I-ORG
''	O
Duellman	O
,	O
1980	O
	
Çıraqlı	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Lachin	I-LOC
	
''	O
Phragmatiphila	B-LOC
nexa	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Hübner	O
,	O
1808	O
)	O
	
Pietro	B-PER
Nardini	I-PER
(	O
1722–1793	O
)	O
	
Rajkot	B-ORG
Junction	I-ORG
railway	I-ORG
station	I-ORG
	
1997	O
:	O
Alan	B-PER
Dershowitz	I-PER
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
Venezuela	B-LOC
.	O
	
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
Route	I-ORG
237	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Girls	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
Generation	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
Teddy	B-PER
Robin	I-PER
as	O
Mr	O
.	O
	
Jogendra	B-PER
Nath	I-PER
Mandal	I-PER
(	O
1904–1968	O
)	O
	
Mozdok–Makhachkala–Kazi	B-ORG
Magomed	I-ORG
pipeline	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Daytime	B-ORG
Emmy	I-ORG
Awards	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
	
23	O
September	O
–	O
Christian	B-PER
K.	I-PER
Cagle	I-PER
	
Erik	B-PER
Engstrom	I-PER
,	O
CEO	O
of	O
Reed	B-ORG
Elsevier	I-ORG
	
Don	B-ORG
Bosco	I-ORG
Preparatory	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
(	O
Ramsey	B-LOC
)	O
	
Olmstead	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
He	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
General	B-ORG
Motors	I-ORG
first	O
,	O
next	O
Chrysler	B-ORG
,	O
Ford	B-ORG
and	O
then	O
to	O
Europe	B-LOC
.	O
	
The	B-PER
Smug	I-PER
E.P	I-PER
.	I-PER
	
Two	O
years	O
later	O
Seán	B-PER
Lemass	I-PER
took	O
over	O
from	O
Éamon	B-PER
de	I-PER
Valera	I-PER
as	O
Taoiseach	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
modernising	O
process	O
began	O
.	O
	
``	O
One	B-ORG
Mint	I-ORG
Julep	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1961	O
)	O
	
*January	O
16	O
–	O
Zelous	B-PER
Wheeler	I-PER
	
Communist	B-ORG
Labour	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Turkey	I-ORG
	
It	O
was	O
won	O
with	O
61	O
%	O
of	O
the	O
votes	O
by	O
Pier	B-PER
Luigi	I-PER
Bersani	I-PER
,	O
who	O
defeated	O
Matteo	B-PER
Renzi	I-PER
in	O
the	O
run-off	O
.	O
	
found	O
2	O
exemplars	O
in	O
Sardinia	B-LOC
.	O
	
Rose	B-LOC
Canyon	I-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
	
Brown-breasted	B-LOC
bamboo	I-LOC
tyrant	I-LOC
	
*****	O
Charles	B-PER
III	I-PER
,	I-PER
King	I-PER
of	I-PER
Spain	I-PER
(	O
1716-1788	O
)	O
	
Wiffi	B-PER
Smith	I-PER
won	O
the	O
event	O
.	O
	
Oswego	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
(	O
1	O
seat	O
)	O
	
The	B-PER
Rev.	I-PER
Richard	I-PER
Coles	I-PER
	
She	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Argentina	B-LOC
in	O
1969	O
and	O
renamed	O
.	O
	
Dave	B-PER
Allen	I-PER
(	I-PER
comedian	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
It	O
was	O
determined	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
carved	O
from	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Chinga	B-LOC
meteorite	I-LOC
.	O
	
Malden	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Missouri	I-LOC
	
''	O
Running	B-ORG
Man	I-ORG
(	O
Episode	O
232	O
)	O
	
He	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Aldo	B-PER
Rossi	I-PER
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
pupil	O
.	O
	
Volume	B-ORG
4	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Hard	I-ORG
Walls	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Little	I-ORG
Trips	I-ORG
	
Blue	B-ORG
Chip	I-ORG
Casino	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Hotel	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Spa	I-ORG
—	O
Michigan	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Indiana	I-LOC
	
Watkins	B-LOC
Glen	I-LOC
International	I-LOC
(	O
5	O
)	O
	
Empress	B-PER
Dowager	I-PER
Ma	I-PER
(	I-PER
Southern	I-PER
Ming	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Fort	B-LOC
Dodge	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
United	I-LOC
States	I-LOC
Army	I-LOC
Post	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
King	B-ORG
Baudouin	I-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
,	O
Brussels	B-LOC
(	O
H	O
)	O
	
Gierwaty	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Maków	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
	
Harrison	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC
	
**	O
Botswana	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Development	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG
Workers	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
Union	I-ORG
	
''	O
Football	B-ORG
League	I-ORG
2	I-ORG
:	O
1	O
''	O
'	O
	
F.	B-PER
M.	I-PER
G.	I-PER
Ozorio	I-PER
	
In	O
1926	O
he	O
was	O
promoted	O
to	O
the	O
rank	O
of	O
Marshal	B-PER
of	I-PER
Italy	I-PER
.	O
	
Ilya	B-PER
Salkind	I-PER
and	O
Pierre	B-PER
Spengler	I-PER
	
''	O
Bob	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Burgers	I-ORG
''	O
	
'	O
''	O
Darren	B-PER
Morgan	I-PER
''	O
'	O
9–3	O
Anthony	B-PER
Davies	I-PER
	
Alejandro	B-PER
Ferrant	I-PER
y	I-PER
Fischermans	I-PER
	
Powderhouse	B-ORG
Hill	I-ORG
—	O
South	B-LOC
Berwick	I-LOC
	
It	O
is	O
within	O
Flathead	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Montana	I-LOC
.	O
	
''Zigeunerweisen	O
,	O
op.20	O
''	O
by	O
Pablo	B-PER
de	I-PER
Sarasate	I-PER
	
172d	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Support	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
	
•	O
Jarčujak	B-LOC
(	O
836	O
)	O
	
Newcastle	B-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
	
Phil	B-PER
Davies	I-PER
(	I-PER
rugby	I-PER
union	I-PER
born	I-PER
1981	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
Aldo	B-PER
Puccinelli	I-PER
(	O
1975	O
)	O
	
The	O
first	O
to	O
provide	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
William	B-PER
of	I-PER
Jumièges	I-PER
.	O
	
Mary	B-PER
Ellen	I-PER
Pleasant	I-PER
	
Listed	B-ORG
buildings	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
Crawley	I-ORG
	
List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
extrasolar	I-ORG
planets	I-ORG
	
Echo	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Los	I-LOC
Angeles	I-LOC
	
``	O
Fall	B-ORG
Back	I-ORG
Down	I-ORG
''	O
	
Țiganu	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Iaz	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
Four	O
singers	O
sang	O
at	O
the	O
concert	O
:	O
Chata	B-PER
,	O
Lia	B-PER
,	O
Rita	B-PER
,	O
and	O
Tomoe	B-PER
Tamiyasu	I-PER
.	O
	
East	B-ORG
Lawrencetown	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Nova	I-ORG
Scotia	I-ORG
	
The	O
original	O
owner	O
was	O
United	B-ORG
Newspapers	I-ORG
who	O
then	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
EMAP	B-ORG
in	O
1991	O
.	O
	
**	O
Henry	B-PER
John	I-PER
Temple	I-PER
,	I-PER
3rd	I-PER
Viscount	I-PER
Palmerston	I-PER
(	O
1855–1858	O
)	O
	
Between	O
1785	O
and	O
1818	O
he	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
tutor	O
to	O
the	O
Branicki	B-ORG
family	O
in	O
Białystok	B-LOC
.	O
	
*069	O
1973E	O
Taku	B-PER
Miki	I-PER
for	O
'	O
''	O
'	O
(	O
)	O
	
''	O
Bryotropha	B-LOC
similis	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Stainton	O
,	O
1854	O
)	O
	
Claudio	B-PER
Bravo	I-PER
(	I-PER
painter	I-PER
)	I-PER
	
''	O
Dorymyrmex	B-LOC
coniculus	I-LOC
''	O
Santschi	O
,	O
1922	O
	
Treat	O
Huey]]	O
Frederik	B-PER
Nielsen	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Ashvin	B-PER
Raja	I-PER
as	O
Paalpandi	O
	
Hapeville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Georgia	I-LOC
–	O
$	O
15,793	O
	
''	O
Eilema	B-ORG
depressa	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Esper	O
,	O
1787	O
)	O
	
Jurassic	B-LOC
5	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
EP	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
	
It	O
is	O
found	O
on	O
Borneo	B-LOC
,	O
Bali	B-LOC
and	O
the	O
Philippines	B-LOC
.	O
	
(	O
16	O
)	O
Kyle	B-PER
Legault	I-PER
	
*Marathon	O
:	O
'	O
''	O
2:13:42	O
hrs	O
''	O
'	O
–	O
Santa	B-LOC
Rosa	I-LOC
,	O
23	O
April	O
2000	O
	
Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Archdiocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Gaeta	I-LOC
	
He	O
died	O
at	O
Ealing	B-LOC
,	O
Middlesex	B-LOC
,	O
on	O
8	O
January	O
1982	O
.	O
	
Thổ	B-LOC
Chu	I-LOC
Island	I-LOC
	
Al-Alam	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
	
'	O
''	O
Conamail	B-PER
mac	I-PER
Faílbi	I-PER
''	O
'	O
	
Haltom	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Texas	I-LOC
	
''	O
Copán	B-LOC
''	O
'	O
–	O
Uaxaclajuun	B-PER
Ub'aah	I-PER
K'awiil	I-PER
(	O
675–738	O
)	O
	
Francisco	B-PER
Menéndez	I-PER
Márquez	I-PER
	
Communist	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Nepal	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
UML	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
*Written	O
by	O
Val	B-PER
Guest	I-PER
and	O
Leslie	B-PER
Thomas	I-PER
	
Hirmand	B-ORG
River	I-ORG
:	O
Iran	B-LOC
and	O
Afghanistan	B-LOC
	
Haoud	B-LOC
El	I-LOC
Hamra	I-LOC
to	O
Arzew	B-LOC
	
Reservoir	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Baltimore	I-LOC
	
Harlingen	B-LOC
(	O
72.76	O
%	O
)	O
	
Aimophila	B-ORG
botterii	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Botteri	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
sparrow	I-LOC
)	O
	
William	B-PER
Lane	I-PER
Craig	I-PER
	
Nee	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
band	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
	
Tulane	B-LOC
/	I-LOC
Gravier	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
